Ball one to Johnny Damon and we are under way.
尼.戴蒙打 一那 我正在D播
Damon has eight hits in 18 at bats,
戴蒙的18打抵杏8支安打
a double, a triple, a couple of stolen bases.
一支二景泊 一支三景泊 纱伪I
He had four hits in the series opener.
他在季首霰荣中舫4支安打
Strike.
好球
Down the right-field line, fair off the bat of Damon.
球舻接彝庖斑 戴蒙@支是界惹
It rolls by Spencer.
斯e塞漏接
And Damon will coast into second base with a leadoff double.
第一棒的戴蒙用一支 安打站上了二
Into right-center field, broken bat, it'll fall, a base hit.
球w入中右外野 喟 落下砹 是安打
They waVe around Damon. He will score.
他在示意戴蒙n回本 他要得分了
And Jason Giambi deliVers
苌.吉安比在第一局
with a run-scoring single here in the opening inning.
舫鲆景泊蛩完友回镜梅
And the Athletics haVe taken that 1-nothing lead.
W克m\蛹谊取得1比0I先
Go, come on, now. We gotta spin it.
加油啊 要保住
Let's go, Yankees!
~s洋基 VS W克m\蛹
Bases loaded.
M
The Yankees haVe the tying run at second, down 2-nothing.
洋基如果可以舫龆景泊 就有C追平 F在2比0落後
The A 's are kicking it and throwing it all oVer the field.
\蛹谊漏接 忙得M鲲w球
And it might lead to their elimination if they don't get it right in a hurry.
如果不so{整B 他⒈惶蕴
Hammered down the right-field line. Justice!
重羧敬蚪右外野 Z斯蒂斯
The Yankees haVe taken the lead.
洋基I先了
They're standing, anticipating another trip
他辛⒅ 期待又一次
to the League championship Series.
挺M盟冠的旅程
The Yankees one out away.
洋基只需解Q最後一打者
Eric Byrnes, never with an at bat in Yankee Stadium,
埃Y克.伯恩斯 他在洋基主鲞]有打
and they don't get much bigger than this one.
@次估也不有什N孬@
Or more hectic when you're up there trying to get a job done.
孤注一S也未必有Y果
And they're a strike away.
]棒落空
And they're roaring in the Bronx.
布朗克斯M是g呼（洋基主鏊在地）
Losing the first two games at home in the best-of-fiVe series
洋基在五黾踞岱^中(53伲 的前鲋鍪Ю
The Yankees will defend their title.
洋基⒑葱l自己的冠^
It's okay, Joe, you can leave it on.
]PS  它_著吧
I don't need to watch. Joe, leave it on.
- 我可以不看 -  _著
Okay.
好吧
Imagine how bad it'd be if you were a Yankee player
想像一下 作檠蠡T
and didn't like the taste of champagne.
s不喜g喝香怎Nk
Better ask to get traded.
只能求D吧
You gotta giVe the Yankees...
必o洋基…
- win the big game.
…A得冠
What a series that is gonna be in the next...
接下⑹窃拥谋荣…
You know how many kids are wearing Giambi's...?
你知道有多少孩子穿著吉安比
You know, Oakland Giambi's jerseys and hats and pictures and posters?
吉安比在W克m的\犹咨 帽子 像和海
Those same kids will be booing in July when the Yankees come here.
- 洋基七月磉@Yr@些孩子u一片 - 希望如此
Is it Giambi that's stabbing the back or the Pinstripes on the East coast?
到底是吉安比落井下石 是|岸的~臭商人^分
You can't blame them for pilfering the henhouse.
你不能怪他巧取豪Z
The henhouse is there. I can't blame them?
- Y源[著不能浪M啊 - 什N叫不能怪他
They're offering $ 120 million oVer six years.
六年Y他出了1|2千f美元
The Yankees haVe deeper pockets and they're willing to giVe him money.
~s洋基比我X多 他意o他出大rX
They're pilfering our players.
他在收割我的T
It's like we're a farm system for the new York Yankees.
好像我是~s洋基的菜地似的
How are the guys doing? That was a killer.
- T打得怎N - 他很害
That was a killer. It's a tough one to swallow. It's...
很害 很y啃下 @…
They played great. They played their hearts out.
- 他打得很好 - 就差^B嵫了
They did. They played fantastic. It just didn't fall our way.
他M力了 打得很精彩 只是Y果不M如人意
You'll do better next year. But we were close, though.
- 明年你打得更好 - 不^就差一c啊 是吧
We were so close. Right there.
很接近了 就差一c
Almost had it. You gotta feel good about that.
差c就倮了 你_心的
I feel great about it. I feel great about it.
我_心死了 _心O了
Um...
唔
We're not gonna do better next year.
明年不打得更好
Why not? Well, you know we're being gutted.
- 槭颤N - 你知道我正被人~肉
We're losing Giambi, Damon, Isringhausen.
吉安比 戴蒙和伊斯林豪森都要走了
Done deal. We're in trouble.
都定了 我麻┖艽
You'll find new guys. You found Jason, you found Damon.
你能找到新人的 初就是你lF了苌和戴蒙
I need more money, Steve. Billy.
- 我要更多的Y金 史蒂夫 - 比利
I need more money. We don't have any.
- 我需要X - 我]X了
I can't compete against $ 120 million with $38 million.
我不能用3800f美元去抗衡1|2千f啊
We're not gonna compete with these teams that have big budgets.
我不能和有更大A算的伍比
We're gonna work within the constraints we have,
我必在自己能力冗\作
and you're gonna do the best job that you can recruiting new players.
而你要M全力招募新T
We're not gonna pay $ 17 million to players.
我]法每年付oT1700f
I'm not asking you
我又]要你出…
for 10 or 20, 30 million dollars.
1千f 2千f或3千f
I'm just asking for a bit of help.
我只要求一c椭
Get me a little closer and I will get you that championship team.
再臀乙幌 我就能湍憬M成冠
I mean, this is why I'm here. This is why you hired me.
你雇我就是榱诉@ @就是我的工作
And I gotta ask you, what are we doing here
我要 我在@嘿M什N…
Billy, l... if it's not to win a championship?
- 比利 我... - …如果不是想A冠
I wanna win just as much... That's my bar. My bar is here.
- 我也很想… - 我的目司驮谶@Y @Y
My bar is to take this team to the championship.
目耸шA得冠
Billy, we're a small-market team, and you're a small-market GM.
比利 我是小市銮蜿 你是小市銮蜿的理
I'm asking you to be okay not spending money that I don't have.
我不能付出我]有的X 你面ΜF
And I'm asking you to take a deep breath,
你深呼吸一口
shake off the loss, get back in a room with your guys,
忘掉失 回到Y去
and figure out how to find replacements for the guys we lost
想k法用我手^的X
with the money that we do have.
找到能替代x_T的新人
I'm not leaving here. I'm not... I can't leave here with that.
我不走 我不能就@幼甙
What else can I help you with?
我能湍闶颤N
It's a good offer, and you gotta match it. L...
@_r太好了 你得想k法s超 我…
I need another day.
我需要一crg
His mind's pretty made up. I just think you should know that.
他很Q 我想你明白
I got a call. I'll get you back. I'll let him know.
- 有M 我一捍蚪o你 - 我一定D告他的
Bye.
再
Yeah? Billy, Scott.
- 喂 - 比利 是我 史考特
Just got off the phone with Dan. You didn't.
- 跟丹通了 - 不是吧
I was surprised he called me.
他打o我 我很@
Stop. I got Johnny for 7.5 or he doesn't play anywhere else.
住口 我o尼_r750f 他不e人效力
That's the deal you made. Boston just upped it to 7. 75.
- @是你答的 - 波士D加a到775f
You there?
你在
We had a deal, Scott. We haVe a deal, if it's 8 million.
- 我f好的 史考特 - 是f好了 如果你能加到800f
Oh, man, you played me. I'm just doing my job for my client.
- 夥 你耍我啊 - 我只是榭舴
No, you're playing me, and you're still playing me.
不 你是耍我 而且你F在也在耍我
Congratulations, asshole. You win.
恭喜你 混蛋 你A了
I like guys that got a little hair on their ass.
我喜g屁股上Lc毛的砘
He looks like a Mantle or a Mays, quite frankly.
坦白f 他是曼托或者梅斯那哟蔚
He's got a baseball body. Matty, who do you got?
- 他天生就是棒球手的w魄 - R蒂 你找到l了
I like Geronimo. Yes.
- 我喜g吉拉尼莫 -
The guy's an athlete. Big, fast, talented.
@砘锸呛眠\T K^大 速度快 有天x
Top of my list. Clean-cut, good face.
- 我手Y排第一的 - L得好看 廓r明
Yeah, good jaw. Five-tools guy.
-  下巴很 - 全能型的
Good-Iooking ballplayer. Can he hit?
- L得不e的球手 - 擅L打
He's got a beautiful swing. The ball explodes off his bat.
- 他]棒姿莺芷亮 是吧 苋鹈 - 他能把球打爆
He throws the club head at the ball, and when he connects,
他用棒尖羟 接|到球r
he drives it, it pops off the bat.
他用力舫 球砰地w走
You can hear it all over the ballpark. A lot of pop.
- 整球龆寄苈到 - 糁新屎芨
If he's good, why doesn't he hit good?
如果他很打 槭颤N打得不好
He is a good hitter. He'll be ready.
- 他是好打者 - t早他出^的
He's gonna be a good hitter against big-league arms?
他好得足以抵抗大盟投手
Could be great. I don't think so.
- 不e的 - 我不@N想
Kid needs at bats. Give him 400 at bats, he's gonna get better.
新人需要打 超^四百 他就好
He can play.
他可以打的
He's hit everywhere along the line.
他可以指哪打哪
He's one of our guys.
他就是我要的人
Okay, let's move on.
好 我^m
Artie, who do you like? I like Perez. He's got a classic swing.
- 阿迪 你喜gl - 我喜g佩雷斯 他的羟蜃莺
It's a real clean stroke. I don't know. Can't hit the curveball.
- ^κ峭昝来 - 我不X得 他能打曲球
There's some work to be done, I'll admit that, but he's noticeable.
需要改M 我承J 不^他也值得P注
Got an ugly girlfriend. What's that mean?
- 女朋友很h - 什N意思
Ugly girlfriend means no confidence.
- 女朋友丑C明他]自信 - 好吧
You are full of it. Artie is right. This guy's got an attitude.
你都昏^了 阿迪是Φ @人很有架
An attitude is good.
有架菔呛檬
He walks in a room, his dick's already been there for two minutes.
他就是那N人]走M 已雄L高昂的人
He passes the eye-candy test. Got the looks.
他K非是A而不的 恰恰外型是不e
He's ready to play the part. He just needs playing time.
他已浜昧 就是需要比
I'm just saying, his girlfriend is a six at best.
我只是f他的女朋友RR虎虎
Look, if we're trying to replace Giambi, this guy could be it.
- 如果要代替吉安比 他行 - 巴拉巴拉
I agree with you. La-la-la-la-la.
- 我同意 - 巴拉巴拉巴拉
Damn, Billy, was that a suggestion?
鬼 比利 你是想提建h
Guys, you're just talking.
夥 你就f]完
Talking, "la-la-la-la-la," like this is business as usual.
f啊f 啦啦啦啦 好像@是例行公事
It's not.
但不是
We're trying to solve the problem.
我在努力解Q} 比利
Not like this. You're not looking at the problem.
不是@拥 你都]正}
We're very aware of the problem. I mean...
我很清楚}是什N 我是f…
Okay, good. What's the problem?
好吧 }是什N
Look, Billy, we all understand what the problem is. We have to...
著 比利 我都知道}何在 我必找人代替…
We have to replace three key players in our lineup.
}是我要找人代替 三重要T
Nope. What's the problem?
不 }是什N
We gotta replace these guys with what we have...
山姆f了 我要a上空缺的…
No. What's the problem, Barry?
不 }是什N 瑞
We need 38 home runs, 120 RBIs and 47 doubles to replace.
我需要找到38全敬 120打c 47二景泊
The problem we're trying to solve is that there are rich teams
我要解Q的}是 如果@是有X球
and there are poor teams, then there's 50 feet of crap,
@Y是F 然後下面是f不清的垃圾
and then there's us.
然後才是我
It's an unfair game.
@是不公平的比
And now we've been gutted. We're like organ donors for the rich.
F在我正被人宰割 就像在o富人捐I器官
Boston's taken our kidneys, Yankees have taken our heart.
波士D拿走了我的IK 洋基拿走了我的心K
And you guys sit around
而你坐在@Y
talking the same old "good body" nonsense like we're selling jeans.
f什N"好w魄"的屁 好像我只是在u牛仔
Like we're looking for Fabio.
好像我在找法比W （身材一流的意大利籍男星）
We got to think differently.
我必D思路
We are the last dog at the bowl.
我是吊尾的
You see what happens to the runt of the litter? He dies.
你知道最弱的狗崽 什N下 I死
Billy, that's a very touching story and everything,
比利 @故事很感人 真的
but I think we're all very much aware of what we're facing.
但我想我都很清楚F在的情r
You have a lot of experience and wisdom in this room.
你是我中g最有最有智慧的
You need to have a little faith and let us do the job of replacing Giambi.
你需要ξ有c信心 我找到能代替吉安比的人
Is there another first baseman like Giambi?
有像吉安比@拥囊臼
No, not really. No.
- ]有了 - ]有
If there was, could we afford him? Nope.
- 如果有 我能I得起 - 不行
Then what the fuck are you talking about, man?
那你屁
If we try to play like the Yankees in here,
如果我在@像洋基那有惺
we will lose to the Yankees out there.
在錾衔得一塌T地
Boy, that sounds like fortune-cookie wisdom to me, Billy.
@起硐窨辗旱拇笤而已 比利
No, that's just logic. Who's Fabio?
- 不 @是思考 - l是法比W啊
He's a shortstop. He's a shortstop from Seattle.
他是游羰 西雅D人
Now, this is no time to push the panic button.
F在]rg恐慌了
Our scouts will find players, Player Development will develop them.
比利 我的球探物色球T 然後M行培
We'll teach them to play Oakland A baseball.
我教他成 W克m\蛹谊的球手
With all due respect, we've been doing this a long time.
- 各位… - ]有阂 但我一直@幼龅
Why don't you just let us be responsible for replacing Giambi
你把替代吉安比的事交o我
with who we know that can play?
我去找能偃蔚娜
Easy power. And loose.
- 力道普通 - 垮
Good face.
L得不e
This son of a bitch is going in the first round.
@O子可以M首l容
You're a premium player, Billy.
你是秀的x手 比利
You can run, you can field, you can throw, you can hit,
你能跑 能守 能投 能打
you can hit with power.
可以大力羟
That doesn't come along Very often.
@K不多
This is Tom Martinez, national cross-checker.
- @是姆.R丁人 球探 - 很高dJR你
How you doing? Billy Beane.
- 你好 - 比利.e恩
Nice to meet you.
很高dJR你
It's been a while since I've seen a five-tool guy that can do everything.
已有段rg]看到全能型x手了
I'm hopeful your interest in professional baseball
我期望你加入棒的d趣
is as strong as ours is gonna be in getting you in this upcoming draft.
和我一夂 我可以一同前M
WOMr. Beane?
e恩先生
Mark is ready to see you now.
R克可以您了
How you doing? WOI'm fine.
- 你今天好 - 我很好
Hey, Billy. Hey, Mark.
- 嘿 比利 - 嗨 R克
Good to see you. Please sit down. You too.
到你真高d 坐
These are the guys. Guys, Billy. Boys.
- @是我的夥 夥 @位是比利 - 大家好
How's it going? All right. How you been?
- 近r如何 - 不e 你怎
You're filling out that chair nicely. I got three weeks in it right now.
- 你坐@椅子很像影 - 我已坐了三周了
Good, good, man.
很好 兄弟
Yeah, man. How you doing? Fantastic.
- 嗯 你怎幽 - 很不e
Awesome. Couldn't be better.
- 好O了 - 再好不^了
That's good to hear. I'm not gonna waste your time.
真是好消息 我不想浪M你的rg
You just tell me what you're looking for.
你直接f你要什N吧
Fifty million dollars in additional payroll.
加薪5000f
You should try Giambi.
你找吉安比要
Ouch. I'm sorry. Too soon, right?
- 正中痛 - 抱歉 _玩笑太早了 是吧
I want this to be a friendly meeting.
我想本次面友善一些
It's not all on your shoulders.
但@不全是你的任吧
Where's Steve in this? Steve's great.
- 史蒂夫怎Nf - 史蒂夫]}
He's supportive in rebuilding this team.
他100%全力支持重建伍
That's what we're gonna do.
我正想@N做
So, what are you looking for? A left-handed reliever.
- 那你想要什N - 左投後援投手
I'm thinking Ricardo Rincon.
我想要Y卡多.林康
That's not gonna happen.
不可能的
Not even a discussion?
都不能
Billy, even if you could afford him, respectfully, we love him.
比利 就算你I得起 e介意我@Nf 我也很喜g他
We're not about to let him go.
我不D的
You got this Venezuelan kid coming up.
但你I了北卡_R拉的 委热鹄新人 不是
We had him. We moved him to Detroit.
]e 已Do底特律了
Huh. What else you thinking?
- 哈 - 有什N想法
Outfielders.
外野手
To replace Damon? Yeah.
- 代替戴蒙 -
In your price range? No disrespect. Enough, Mark.
- 就你能出的r格? 我]有阂夤 - 足蛄 R克
Uh... Hollins?
呃...哈林斯?
Uh-uh.
不
Garcia? No.
- 加西? - 不行
Maybe Coste.
那N 科斯特
Uh-uh.
哼
That's it.
只能@恿
All right, tell me about Garcia. To replace Johnny Damon?
- 好吧 就加西吧 - 泶替尼.戴蒙
Mark, is he healthy? Yeah, he's healthy-ish.
- R克 他健康]}吧 -  他正在恢
He had that back thing.
不m你f 他背有c} 是吧
He'll be ready for spring ball. I'll tell you what.
- 春季就能出了 - 我直f吧
I can give you Guthrie if you kick in some cash.
如果你NcX 我可以Q格思Y
Mark Guthrie? Yeah.
- R克.格思Y？ -
How much cash? Two hundred K.
- 多少X - 20f
Okay.
好
So Garcia's gonna be a no. You're kidding me, right?
- 不能o你加西 - 你逗我的吧
You're kidding me. I'm not.
- 你_玩笑 - ]有
Okay. Straight up, Garcia for Guthrie, no kicker.
好吧 加西Q格思Y 不NX
No kicker? Straight up.
- 不NX了? - 一清二楚
I think it's gonna be a hard no on Garcia, but let's just keep going.
加西^Σ恍 但我能e人
What else you thinking? What are we doing? Is this business?
- 你有想要的 - @是致锇 我是在做生意吧
This is the way we do business in Cleveland.
我在克利夫m就@N做生意
Hey.
嘿
Hello. Who are you?
- 你好 - 你是l
I'm Peter Brand.
我是皮特.布m德
What do you do?
你做什N的
I'm special assistant to Mark Shapiro.
我是R克.史派_的特e助理
So, what do you do?
所以 你做什N的
Mostly player analysis right now.
F在基本上是球T分析u估
Been on the job long? First job in baseball?
工作多久了 是在棒球界的第一份工作?
It's my first job anywhere.
@就是我的第一份工作
Wow, congrats. Thank you.
- 哇 恭喜啊 - xx
First job. Whose nephew are you?
第一份工作 你是l的侄子
Why does Mark listen to you?
R克槭颤N你的
I don't think, uh...
我不J椤
I don't think he does very often.
我不J樗常我的
He just did.
但才有
Well, in that circumstance,
在那N情r下
I think he was more listening to Bruce than myself.
我想他其是布斯的 不是我的
Mm-hm. Who are you?
嗯 你是l
I'm Peter Brand.
我是皮特.布m德
I don't give a rat's ass what your name is.
我才他不管你叫什N
What happened in there?
才是怎N回事
What happened in that room?
才在Y面是怎N回事
I'm not quite sure what you're asking me, Mr. Beane.
我不太清楚你想什N e恩先生
What did you tell Bruce?
你跟布斯f了什N
I just told Bruce I like Garcia. You like Garcia. Why?
- 我只是f我喜g加西 - 你槭颤N喜g加西
Why?
槭颤N
I don't know. Ahem.
我不知道
There is an epidemic failure within the game
在@圈子Y 有N蔓延性的
to understand what is really happening.
盲目oF畹牧T
And this leads people who run Major League Baseball teams
@\作棒球大盟的人
to misjudge their players and mismanage their teams.
e`估了自己的球T和伍
I apologize.
真是抱歉
Go on.
^mf
Okay. People who run ball clubs, they think in terms of buying players.
好 I棒球俱凡康哪切┤ 思S是Iu球T
Your goal shouldn't be to buy players. Your goal should be to buy wins.
你的目的不是Iu球T 而是I取倮
And in order to buy wins, you need to buy runs.
要I到倮 就要I得分
You're trying to replace Johnny Damon.
你想找人代替尼.戴蒙
The Red Sox see Johnny Damon
波士Dtm看中尼.戴蒙
and they see a star who's worth $7.5 million a year.
是看到一r值750f美元一年的明星
When I see Johnny Damon,
而我看尼.戴蒙
what I see is...
我看到的是...
an imperfect understanding of where runs come from.
θ绾蔚梅趾o概念的球T
The guy's got a great gloVe.
他是不e的守潢T
He's a decent leadoff hitter. He can steal bases.
是很好的首l打者 他很I
But is he worth the $ 7.5 million a year
但他值波士Dtmo的 每年750f的薪金
No. No.
不 不值
Baseball thinking is medieVal.
棒球的思S在中世o水平
They are asking all the wrong questions.
他的想法都有}
And if I say it to anybody, I'm ostracized. I'm a leper.
如果我@痈嬖Ve人 我就是反优 冒天下之大不t
So that's why I'm cagey about this with you.
所以我才跟你@圈子
That's why...
所以我...
I respect you, Mr. Beane, and if you want full disclosure,
我尊敬你 e恩先生 如果你想掏心C的
I think it's a good thing that you got Damon off your payroll.
我X得你放掉戴蒙是件好事
I think it opens up all kinds of interesting possibilities.
我X得@砗芏嘤腥さ目赡苄
Where you from, Pete? Maryland.
- 你家l是哪 皮特 - RYm
Where'd you go to school? Yale. I went to Yale.
- 你在哪Y上W - 耶 我在耶上W
What'd you study? Economics.
- 你W什N的 - W
I studied economics.
我W的
Yale, economics and baseball.
耶 W 有棒球
You're funny, Pete.
你很有意思 Pete
Tell me, why Billy?
告V我 槭颤N是比利
What is it that makes him special?
是什N他f而出
Very rare do you come upon a young man like Billy
很y遇到比利@拥哪贻p人
who can run, who can field, who can throw, who can hit,
能跑 能守 能投 能打
and who can hit with power.
能舫龊们
Those five tools, you don't see that very often.
@五N技能R 不多的
Most of the youngsters that we have an interest in
我中意的^大部分年px手
have one or two tools,
擅L一或身技能
and we're hoping to develop an extra one.
我希望他能多l展一
Your son has five.
而你的鹤游屙全能
We're looking at a guy that's a potential superstar for us in New York.
我在榧~s找一未淼某巨星
The time is now to get him started.
F在是r候他起w了
We're prepared to make a sizable financial commitment.
我浜昧厚的待遇
The Mets are gonna stand behind Billy
大都全力支持比利
because we expect him to be our big-league center fielder.
因槲期望他成 大盟Y的中鍪
This check here represents the offer
@支票代表了~s大都
that the New York Mets would be making to Billy.
o比利的S厚回
You do know that he's been accepted to Stanford on a full scholarship?
你知道他已得到了 斯坦福大W的全~W金
I do.
我知道
So he can do both?
所以他能擅婕骖了
Unfortunately, he can't do Stanford and professional baseball.
很不幸的 他不能同r 上斯坦福和I棒球
He would have to pick one or the other.
他必有所取
If he wants to be center fielder for the Mets,
如果要大都的中鍪
wants to be a baseball player,
一名棒球\T
he really needs to accept this as life's first occupation, first career.
他必⒋俗槿松第一位的事I和I
We're all told at some point we can no longer play the children's game.
某r刻有人告V我 不能再玩小孩子的[蛄
We just don't know when that's gonna be.
只是我不清楚是什Nr刻
Some of us are told at 18, some of us are told at 40, but we're all told.
有些人18q就到 有些人40q才知道 但有那r候
But this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
@是一生一次的C遇
We want you badly, and we think that this amount of money expresses that desire.
我很看好你 而@PX的的 充分表_了我的渴望
Billy, this is your decision, and whatever that decision is,
比利 @是你的x 不^o你怎NQ定
you know it's fine with your mother and I.
我和你都]有意
Hello? Hey, it's Billy Beane.
- 喂 - 嘿 我是比利 e恩
Hey, what time is it? I don't know.
- F在c啊 - 我不知道
Listen, would you have drafted me in the first round?
著 第一x秀你挑我
What?
什N
After I left, you looked me up on your computer.
我x_之後 你在X上查^我
Would you have drafted me in the first round?
第一x秀你挑我岚
I did, yeah. You were a good player.
的 你是好球手
Cut the crap, man.
e胡扯 夥
Would you have drafted me in the first round?
第一x秀你挑我岚
I'd haVe taken you in the ninth round. No signing bonus.
我把你排到第九 ]有s金
I imagine you would'Ve passed and taken that scholarship.
我猜你放 接受斯坦福的W金
Yeah.
]e
Pack your bags, Pete.
打包吧 皮特
I just bought you from the Cleveland Indians.
我目死夫m印第安手上I了你
Is it attached to that clamp? Yeah, let me unhook it.
- @是B著那A子 -  我斫忾_
Slide it up right there.
哪茄Y滑下
To the left. I did.
- 到左 - 我是啊
Yeah, yeah. Hang on, it's wet.
- 好 好 - 等等 有c
Come on.
放吧
Morning, Suzanne. Coffee on? Yes.
- 早安 K珊 咖啡好了 -
Great.
很好
Billy Beane's office. Hey.
- 比利.e恩k公室 - 嘿
Peter Brand. Billy.
- 皮特.布m德 - 比利
How are...? Hi, how you doing? Nice to see you.
- 你好…嗨 你好 - 到你真_心
Good to have you here. Boy, you move in fast.
你能碚婧 你幼髡婵彀
Yeah, yeah. I got here early this morning.
我今早到的
All moved in. Yeah.
- 都搬好了 - 不e
Yeah.
是啊
Hey, Billy,
嗨 比利
I wanted you to see these player evaluations
我希望你看看
that you asked me to do.
你要我做的球Tu估
I asked you to do three.
我要你u估三
To evaluate three players. Yeah.
- u估三球T - 是啊
How many did you do?
你做了
Okay.
不e
Actually, 51. I don't know why I lied just then.
其是51 我不知道才槭颤N撒e
Why don't you walk me through the board?
你陪我去分牌下走走吧
Thank you.
xx
Using this equation in the upper left,
用左上角的@方程式
I'm projecting that we need to win at least 99 games
我J槲至少需要A99霰荣
in order to make it to the postseason.
才能打入季後
We need to score at least 814 runs in order to win those games
要A@N多 我至少拿下814分
and allow no more than 645 runs.
最多只能645分
What's this?
@是什N
This is a code that I'Ve written for our year-to-year projections.
是我做的年度球Tu估t
This is building in the intelligence that we haVe to project players.
是根我掌握的所有 YηTM行u估
Okay.
然後呢
It's about getting things down to one number.
就是⒏鞣N信息底只
Using the stats the way we read them,
通^我特有的分析
we'll find Value in players that nobody else can see.
就lFe人看不到的 球T的在r值
People are oVerlooked
有的人才因
for a Variety of biased reasons and perceiVed flaws.
各N偏和外在的缺c被忽
Age, appearance, personality.
比如年g 外貌 性格
Bill James and mathematics cut straight through that.
比.詹姆斯\用W摒@些因素
Billy, of the 20,000 notable players for us to consider,
比利 在我u估的2f球T中
I believe that there is a championship team
我相信就有我付得起的25
of 25 people that we can afford,
可以M建一支Z冠的球T
because everyone else in baseball undervalues them.
因槠渌I热耸慷嫉凸懒怂
Like an island of misfit toys.
他就像被孤立的不匹配玩具
Billy, this is chad Bradford. He's a relief pitcher.
比利 @是查德.布拉德福 他是後援投手
He is one of the most undervalued players in baseball.
他就是最被低估的球T之一
His defect is that he throws funny.
他的缺c是投球幼骱芑稽
Nobody in the big leagues cares about him because he looks funny.
就因樗幼骰稽 棒球大盟]人看重他
This guy could be not just the best pitcher in our pen,
如果在我手上 @砘⒉恢皇亲罴淹妒
but one of the most effectiVe relief pitchers in all baseball.
而成樗有棒球比中 最牛的後援投手
This guy should cost $3 million a year.
@人值得年薪300f美金
We can get him for 237,000.
我出23f7就能下他
Billy.
比利
That it? Yeah.
- 就是@ - 是
Hey, Art.
嗨 艾特
Can I talk to you before you get started?
可以在你_前和你
I'm a bit busy right now. I know.
- 我F在有c忙 - 我知道
I know. Okay.
- 我知道 - 好吧
Morning, everyone. Art.
- 大家早上好 - 艾特
Peter Brand. Nice to meet you. Where the hell's Pete?
- 皮特.布m德 很高d到你 - 皮特死哪喝チ
That's Pete.
@位是皮特
Grab a seat. I'll be right back.
找座位 我R上回
All right, where did you say he's at?
行了 你f他在哪碇
Okay. He's on...
嗯 他在...
Who's the kid? A friend of mine.
- 那小子是l - 是我朋友
I can't manage this team under a one-year contract.
只一年合同 我]法指н@支
Well, sure you can.
你然可以
No, I can't.
不 我不行
Okay. I gotta put a team on the field.
好吧 我要拉一去比
After that, I'll take a good long look at your contract.
之後 我仔看看你的合同
Deal with the manager's contract, then put a team on the field.
先和球理s 然後再M①怎N
At this moment, if a grounder's hit to first, nobody's there to stop it.
艾特 F在如果地L球被舻揭 ]人接得住
It's not easy doing what I do under the cloud of a one-year contract.
在只一年合s的毫ο 治疫@份活可不容易
Okay, I understand that.
行了 我能理解
I've been there. I know you have.
- 我也有^@Nv - 我知道 我知道你也有^
A one-year contract means the same thing to a manager as to a player.
一年合sηT和 球理意味著同拥毫
There's not a lot of faith there.
我]有信心
Which is strange after a 102-win season.
上季A了102 有@拥慕Y果真是奇怪
I see.
明白了
If you lose the last game of the season, nobody gives a shit.
你要是了季最後那鲎钪匾的 前面的倮就]人在乎了
So it's on me now? No, Art, it's on me.
- @NfF在任在我了 - 不 艾特 是我的任
And the kid is the new assistant GM.
@小伙是新淼慕理助理
Okay. Okay, fellas.
- 好吧 - 行了 各位
Hey, Billy.
嗨 比利
You can't deny his offensive output. He can play.
你不能否J他的攻袅 他有一手
And we need people that can play.
我需要打球的人
Who do you wanna talk about first?
你想先l
None of them.
一都不想
Billy, we got 38 home runs, 120 RBIs to make up for.
比利 我差38本敬 和120打c
Guys, you're still trying to replace Giambi.
各位 你是在找人取代吉安比
I told you we can't do it, and we can't do it.
我告V^你我做不到 我不能@N干
Now, what we might be able to do is re-create him.
F在我能做的是再造一他
Re-create him in the aggregate. The what?
- 在瞪显僭焖 - 在什N上
Giambi's on-base percentage was.477.
吉安比的上韭适.477
Damon's on-base, .324. And Olmedo's was.291.
戴蒙是.324 W梅多是.291
Add that up and you get...
加起硎...
Do you want me to speak?
你是要我f
When I point at you, yeah.
我指著你的r候 是的
1.092. Divided by three.
- 1.092 - 除以3
.364. That's what we're looking for.
- .364 - @就是我要的
Three ballplayers... Three ballplayers whose average OBP is...
三球T 三平均上韭适...
.364.
.364
Wait, that doesn't come out right. It's right, Artie.
- 慢著 @N算不 - ]e的 阿迪
Billy. You gotta carry the one.
- 比利 - 你要加上@
Billy. Scratch this out.
- 比利 - 把@去掉
Yeah?
什N
Who's that?
那是l
That's Pete.
那是皮特
Does Pete really need to be here?
@Y需要皮特
Yes, he does.
需要
Okay, here's who we want.
好了 @些就是我要的人
Jason's little brother, Jeremy.
1: 苌的弟弟 苋鹈
Oh, God. Billy, that's trouble.
- 天啊 - 比利 @可有麻
Billy, look, if l... Yeah. Billy, if I may, he's had his problems off the field,
比利 如果我...我能插一句 他的}在鐾
and we know what he can't do on the field.
而且我知道他在錾系娜觞c
He's getting thick around the waist.
他都_始l福了
There's reports about him on weed, in strip clubs.
有蟮勒f他吸大麻 出入衣舞俱凡
His on-base percentage is all we're looking at now.
他的上韭示褪俏F在要找的
And Jeremy gets on base an awful lot for a guy who only costs 285,000.
相於他那28.5f的身r 苋鹈椎纳韭在很可^
Jeez, Billy... Number two:
- 天呢 比利... - 2
David Justice. Oh, no.
- 大l.Z斯蒂斯 - 哦 不要吧
His legs are gone. Not a good idea.
- 他的腿]用了 - @主意很
Old Man Justice? Why is that?
- 老人Z斯蒂斯? - 怎N@Nf
Steinbrenner's so pissed at his decline, he's willing to eat his contract to get rid of him.
施泰因布{於他的退步很怒 他情o`s金⑺逐出
Exactly. Ten years ago, Justice, big name.
- f得好 - 十年前 大l.Z斯蒂斯的名字的
Been in big games.
⒓恿撕芏嘀匾事
He's gonna really help our season tickets early in the year,
季初⑹俏的票房大u狳c
but in the dog days in July, August, we're lucky if he's gonna hit his weight.
但到了七八月的三伏天 他可以保持w重我就走\了
Billy, his legs are gone, and he's a defensive liability.
比利 他腿都]用了 他是防守的累
I question whether the bat speed's there.
我都岩伤的羟蛩偈遣皇窃诮≡
His legs are gone. Grady.
- 他的腿]用了 - 格雷迪
We'll be lucky to get 60 games out of him. Why do you like him?
他能上60霰荣就很走\了 你看中他什N了
Because he gets on base.
因樗上韭矢
What is this? What are we doing?
- @算什N - 我在致
Okay, number three:
好了 三
Scott Hatteberg. Who?
- 斯科特.哈特伯格 - l
Hatteberg? Exactly.
- 哈特伯格？ - 正是
He sounds like an Oakland A already.
他起砭拖袷W克m\蛹谊球T
Yes, he's had a little problem with... Little problem? He can't throw.
- ]e 他有c小}... - 小}? 他不能扔球
He's a career.260 hitter. The best part of his career is over.
他的羟蚵适.260 他的IS金期已Y束了
It's just getting started. Boston wants to cut him.
- 我f才要_始 - 波士D不想要他了
No one wants to pick him up. Good. He's cheap.
- 可]人想他回去 - @ξ是好事 他很便宜
Let me get this straight. You're gonna get a guy
我把事情搞清楚 你要一
that's been released by half the organizations in baseball
被半蛋羟蚵盟球放的人
because he's got nonrepairable nerve damage in his elbow and can't throw.
因樗的肘部受^不可治K的 神pе滤不能扔球
He can't throw and he can't field. But what can he do?
他不能扔球又不能接防 他能致锬
Oh, boy.
各位
Check your reports or I'm gonna point at Pete.
查查你的Y料 否t我就皮特了
He gets on base. He can get on base.
- 他能上 - 他能上
So he walks a lot. He gets on base a lot, Rocco.
- 他是保送次刀喟 - 他上敬刀 洛克
Do I care if it's a walk or a hit?
我需要在乎是保送是安打
Pete?
皮特
You do not. I do not.
- 你不需要 - 我不需要
I got 37 free agents that are better than those three guys.
比利我有37比@三砘 更好的自由球T
Wait a minute, let me get this straight.
等一下 我再搞明白了
So you're not gonna bring in one
就是f榱颂Q吉安比
but three defective players to replace Giambi?
你要下不止一 而是三次品球T
You're not buying into this Bill James bullshit?
你不是相信了比.詹姆斯 那套鬼了吧
This is the new direction of the A's.
@是W克m\蛹谊的新方向
We are card counters at the blackjack table
我是桌上的算牌客
and we're gonna turn the odds on the casino.
我要A^f家
I don't see it. Seriously, guys.
- 我不懂 - f到^ 夥
I think we have to remember this is the man.
我想我需要住 他是我的ь^人
He answers to no one except ownership and God.
他只需ν顿Y人和上帝
And he doesn't have to answer to us.
他]必要ξ有交待
We make suggestions, he makes decisions.
我提建h 他碜Q定
That's all fine and well, but we've been working our asses off
既然@诱f 我榱 @俱凡扛好
for weeks to make this club better, and you're shitting all over it.
I心r血了六半周 你s不屑一
This is not a discussion.
@不是在
What are we discussing?
那我在f什N
Barry, not a discussion.
瑞 不是
Billy, man, um,
比利 夥
there's one thing you're forgetting.
我想你忘了一件事
None of those three guys knows how to play first base.
@三人都不知道怎N守一
Well, you're gonna have to teach one of them.
你得教他中的一
Teach?
教?
Which one?
教哪
This is really the kickoff to the holiday season here in downtown Seattle.
@是西雅D市^度假季的重^
It took weeks of planning to lead up to the big event, but it was well worth it.
@盛事已I淞字 但一切等待都是值得的
The weather was ideal. People are still haVing a great time.
天夂O了 人玩得高d
Thousands of people were out earlier.
成千上f的人早早就出T了
We haVe a nice recap for you
正在槟悴蟮氖
of all the great events taking place downtown in Seattle...
在西雅D市中心e行的盛事
Hello? Scott?
- 喂 - 斯科特
Yes.
是我
It's Billy Beane of the Oakland A 's. Yes.
- 我是W克m\蛹谊的比利.e恩 - 你好
Can we talk? Uh, yeah.
- 可以 - 然
Do you wanna let us in?
你能我M
Pardon me? We're out front.
- 你f什N - 我就在外面
What? On the curb.
- 什N - 在路
Uh, yeah, yeah.
哦 好的 好的
Honey?
H鄣
Oh, thank you. Thank you, ma'am.
xx xx 夫人
Very kind.
真客
How's the elbow, Scott?
手肘好些了 斯科特
You know, it's good. It's really good. It's great. Uh...
挺好 很好 好O了
I can't throw the ball at all. Yeah.
- 我根本扔不了球 - 知道
You've thrown your last ball from behind home plate.
你最後一次扔球是谋景遽崦
That's what I'd say. Well...
我就想@Nf
Good news is, we want you at first.
好消息是 我要你守一
We want you to play first base for the Oakland A's.
我想要你W克m\蛹谊的一臼
Okay, well,
@...
I've only ever played catcher.
我只^捕手
Scott, you're not a catcher anymore.
斯科特 你再也不是捕手了
If you were, our call wouldn't have been the only one you got.
如果你是 我就不是 唯一o你打的人了
Yeah. Hey, listen, no, I appreciate it. You're welcome.
-  著 我很感激你的P注 - 不用x
But the thing is, is... You don't know how to play first base.
- 但}是... - 你不知道怎N守一
Scott. That's right.
- 斯科特 - ]e
It's not that hard, Scott.
]那Ny的 斯科特
Tell him, Wash. It's incredibly hard.
- 告V他 A叔 - 是非常y
Hey, anything worth doing is. And we're gonna teach you.
任何有意x的事都不容易 我教你的
Wait a minute here. I mean, but what about...?
等一下 我是f 那...
Jason's gone, Scott.
苌走了 斯科特
You want me to take Giambi's spot at first base?
你想要我取代吉安比的一疚
Yeah. What about the fans?
- ]e - 球迷怎Nf
Maybe I can teach one of them. The fans don't... Good one.
- 也S我也能教教他 - 球迷不...f得好
Fans don't run my ball club.
我的俱凡坎皇怯汕蛎越I
Honey, what are you doing awake?
你怎N醒了
Sweetheart, can you?
H鄣 麻┠...
That's my daughter.
那是我女
You got kids?
你有孩子
Uh, yeah, a daughter.
有 一女
Scott, this is a contract to play ball for the Oakland A's.
斯科特 @是W克m\蛹谊打球的合s
A copy's been sent over to your agent.
送了副本o你的o人
Discuss with your wife, let us know.
和你妻子商量一下 告V我Y果
Thank you.
xx
Bye-bye. Bye.
再
Oh, and, Scott. Yeah?
- 哦 α 斯科特 - 嗯？
Don't tell anyone about the first-base thing.
不要告V任何人一镜氖虑
Yes, sir. Okay.
好的 先生
Happy holidays. All right.
- 假期愉快 - 好的
Hey, Sharon. Hi, Billy.
- 嗨 莎 - 你好 比利
Is she ready? She's out with friends.
- 她浜昧 - 她和朋友出去了
But she'll be back. Come in.
但她R上回 M戆
Okay. Yeah, she's right here. Hold on.
- 好的 - 她就在@ 等等
Here you go.
o你
Here, wanna have a seat? Yeah.
- 坐 - 好的
You good, Billy? Yeah. How are you, Alan?
- 你好 比利 - 挺好 你呢 艾
Good. Really good. Things are peaceful around here.
挺好 真的挺好 @地方很安o
It's good to see you.
到你真好
Thanks, Alan.
xx 艾
I haven't got to see you since play-offs.
季Y束後我就]^你了
I wanted to say that New York was heartbreaking.
我得f~s是心地
I'm sure for you too.
δ愣言肯定如此
Not many teams make it that far, and to watch you go that far was...
]字球能拼到那 看到你打M去了 真是...
It was really an accomplishment. Well, that's nice.
- _值貌诲e - xx褒
How is the team shaping up?
球涞迷觞N恿
Team's good. Rebuilding. Good.
- 不e 正在重M - 很好啊
I read you lost Giambonni and Damon.
我看蠹上f你失去了吉安搏比和戴蒙
Giambi. Giambi.
- 是吉安比 - 吉安比
Yeah. Damon, Isringhausen.
]e 有戴蒙和伊斯林豪森
They're really...? They're gone? Gone. Yesterday's news.
- 他真的...走了? - 走了 不是新r事了
That's terrible. No, but that is a tough situation.
- 那太可怕了 - ]有啦 但形莸拇_谰
That's...
真是...
You're gonna be fine, though. You always figure something out.
不^你好起淼 你能把事情搞定
Where is she? Where was she? Down the street or?
- 她到哪 - 在街^是
Oh, sorry, yeah. I just talked to her on her cell. She's coming up the hill.
Σ黄  我打了她手C 她正要上山
Okay.
好吧
She's got a cell phone?
她有手C了?
Yeah. A 12-year-old?
- 是的 - 12q就配手C?
Yeah.
是的
Huh.
哈
For emergencies.
以防f一
Big parenting decision.
家L的重大Q定
But it's something that, you know, we, you know, all should discuss,
但那是...我...那 我一起的事
because if you have any objections, of course...
如果你有任何反σ庖...
Her mother and I will discuss it.
我和她商量的
But thank you.
但xx你
Any of these? Um...
有喜g的
I don't know.
我不知道
Do you...? This one's cool.
@不e
Is that good or bad?
好是不好啊
Butterflies. They're okay.
- 蝴蝶 - 看起聿诲e
Look, that one's pretty. I like the red.
看 那好看 我喜gt色的
Should we try?
我?
No?
不要
Oh, I like this one. Yeah?
- 我喜g@ - 是
Dad, look at this one.
爸爸 你看@
Look how it's red. It's beautiful.
- 看它的t色 - 真漂亮
This one's pretty. Let's try it out.
- @好看 - 我碓
Just right here? Why don't we go over there?
就在@
Can we go over there?
去那好
Oh, honey, you need to sing. That's so good.
H鄣 你唱出戆 唱得那N好
That's beautiful.
真好
Sometimes I sing.
我有r也唱
It's fun to sing with your song, but I don't want people to listen to me.
唱歌很有意思 但我不想e人到我唱歌
Well, honey, I think people would love to listen to you. That's beautiful.
H鄣 我想人 喜g你唱的 很好
Would you sing a little for your dad?
可以榘职殖一小段
Right here in the middle of the store?
就在@Y 商店Y
Little bit. Little bit.
- 就唱拙 - 就拙
You ready? I'm ready.
- 浜昧 - 好了
Okay.
好吧
* I'm just a little bit Caught in the middle *
* 我有c左右呻y *
* Life is a maze And love is a riddle *
* 生活是座迷m 凼i *
* I don't know where to go Can't do it alone, I've tried *
* 我不知道去哪 我o法自完成 我努力了 *
* And I don't know why *
* 我不知道槭颤N *
* I'm just a little girl Lost in the moment *
* 我只是迷失在此刻的小女孩 *
* I'm so scared But I don't show it *
* 管害怕但我s不流露 *
* I can't figure it out It's bringing me down *
* 我]有k法 快被艨 *
* I know I've got to let it go *
* 我知道我得放手 *
* And just enjoy the show **
* 好好享受@鲂 *
I think this is a steal, to get Billy Beane.
我想有人要把比利.e恩走
He's young, he's talented.
他年p 有才能
A true fiVe-tool player with speed. This guy is a can't-miss prospect.
一速度型的五全能球T 他是不容e^的力股
This is a great sign for the new York Mets.
@~s大都碚f是很好的E象
And it could be the turnaround that they'Ve been looking for.
f不定就是他一直在で蟮霓DC
Ball one.
那
I'll take Billy Beane oVer Strawberry.
我看好比利.e恩
Billy Beane, an interesting pick, turned down a scholarship.
比利.e恩做了有意思的x 他拒^了W金
He could'Ve gone to Stanford.
他本砜梢匀ニ固垢４W
Sometimes you don't find out till you get to the big leagues...
有r你要到了大盟才明白
Strike!
好球
This guy has never failed at anything. He's coming out of high school.
@砘]有失∵^ 他高中I
Billy was gonna go to college. He could'Ve been a great quarterback.
比利本硪去上大W 他可以成橐幻出色的橄烨蛩姆中l
Strike three.
三振出局
There's not an organization in baseball
任何一棒球球
who would not haVe taken a chance on this young guy.
都意把涸谶@年p人身上
He didn't pan out. That happens every year.
他]成功 每年都有@拥睦子
Some do, some don't.
有些成功 有些失×
I mean, if you're haVing any doubt at all about this...
我是f 如果你@Q定不_定...
HaVing the scholarship...
P於W金的...
Your son was born with a God-giVen ability.
你鹤佑刑熨x
Few scouts can go into the mind of a young man
很少有球探能探知一年p人的想法
and determine whether he's really confident about what he can do.
砼嗨是否真的ψ约旱哪芰τ行判
A Very special player.
一很特e的球T
So you can sign him based on his ability,
所以你可以根他的能力s
but then he's gotta be successful to be confident.
之後他就得成功得自信起
And once he becomes confident, that's when you'Ve got something.
他一旦有了自信 你就有盼^了
You make a decision on what you see.
你根眼的做出Q定
And if things don't pan out, you moVe on.
如果不成功 你就得往前看
That's baseball.
@就是棒球
Many are called, few are chosen.
很多人到了召 那能被x中的s是e
Billy, that is Kevin Youkilis. That is the Greek God of Walks.
比利 @是P文.尤克Y斯 被Q^「希D保送之神」 （尤克力斯是希D名 他上韭O高）
That's my hero.
他是我的偶像
That man gets walked more than anybody in baseball
他得到的保送上敬 是除了瑞.邦以外
except for Barry Bonds.
最多的
I tried to convince Shapiro to pick him up last June,
去年6月我Df服史派_下他
but he said he waddled like a duck.
但他f他走路u[像只子
Yeah, Boston snagged him.
Y果波士D走了他
I think they wanna wait and see.
我想他是想^望一下
Are you okay, Billy? Billy?
- 你好 比利 - 比利
Can we talk?
我可以
Yeah. Yeah.
可以 好的
You're unhappy, Grady. Why?
你不_心 格雷迪 怎N了
Wow.
哇
May I speak candidly? Sure, go ahead.
- 我可以直直f - 然 f吧
Major League Baseball and its fans, they're gonna be more than happy
全美I棒球大盟和它的粉z 很芬獍涯愫凸雀栊∽
to throw you and Google Boy under the bus
扔到巴士下
if you keep doing what you're doing.
如果你照目前@有惺碌脑
You don't put a team together with a computer.
你不能用X去M
No? No.
- 不能 - 不能
Baseball isn't just numbers. It's not science.
棒球不只是底 不是一T科W
If it was, anybody could do what we're doing, but they can't.
如果是的 任何人都能做我的工作 但其他做不到
They don't know what we know.
他不知道我所知的
They don't have our experience and our intuition.
他]有我的和直X
Okay.
好吧
You got a kid in there that's got a degree in economics from Yale.
你就靠那有耶大W WW位的小孩
You got a scout here with 29 years of baseball experience.
你面前t是有29年棒球的球探
You're listening to the wrong one.
你xe了⒅\ο
Now, there are intangibles that only baseball people understand.
有些y以捉摸的因素只有刃胁哦
You're discounting what scouts have done for 150 years?
你要低估球探干了150年的活路
Even yourself?
甚至包括你自己
Adapt or die.
mh境 否t死路一l
This is about you and your shit, isn't it?
@是因槟阕约旱慕v 是不是
Twenty years ago, some scout got it wrong.
20年前 有球探看e人了
Whoa. Okay. Okay. Now you declare war on the system.
- 哇 行了 行了 - 你F在是向鹘y正式宣鹆
Okay, okay, my turn. You don't have a crystal ball.
好了 好了 我f删淞 你]有水晶球
You can't look at a kid and predict his future any more than I can.
要看著一人就能Ay他的未 你的本事也不比我多少
I've sat at those kitchen tables with you
我和你一起坐在那些餐桌
and listened to you tell parents, "When I know, I know.
你跟家Lf 「到r候了我自然就知道」
And when it comes to your son, I know."
「你的鹤有胁恍 我一眼就能看出怼
And you don't.
其你做不到
You don't.
你做不到
Okay. I don't give a shit about friendship,
好了 我才不在乎什N友情
this situation, or the past.
不管F在 是那
Major League Baseball thinks the way I think. You're not gonna win.
全美I棒球大盟和我思路一致 你不A的
And I'll give you a nickel's worth of free advice.
我要o你一免M建h
You're never gonna get another job
在你我⒓油赀@K〉馁季 K被老_除後
after this catastrophic season you're about to set us all up for.
你⒃僖舱也坏焦ぷ
You'll have to explain to your kid
你⒉坏貌幌蚰愕暮⒆咏忉
why you're working at Dick's Sporting Goods.
你槭颤N在迪克\佑闷返旯ぷ
I'm not gonna fire you, Grady.
我不炒你~的 格雷迪
Fuck you, Billy. Now I will.
- 操你的 比利 - F在我_了你
Good luck, Art.
祝你好\ 艾特
Kubota. You never played ball, right?
久保田 你]打^棒球
I played a little T-ball. You're the new head scout.
- 打^一c少年棒球 - 你懋首席球探
Congratulations.
恭喜
So Boston's gonna wait and see?
所以波士D正在^望？
Yeah. It's just you and me, Pete.
就你和我 皮特
And we're all in.
我_始吧
It sounds like you're apologizing for what they're doing.
起砗孟衲阍樗的行榈狼
I'm not. I just don't know what you're gonna do
我]有 我只是不明白
with the budget that the A 's haVe. Who are you gonna get?
你能用\蛹谊的 A算做什N 你Il
I'm looking at the spring-training roster.
我看了春季的名
You gotta be kidding me. How so?
- 你直在_玩笑 - 怎N了
He looked like a clown out there.
他在那壕拖小丑
Who? Chad Bradford.
- l - 查德.布拉德福
Tell me about Bradford.
布拉德福情r如何
I like him a little bit, but he's a specialist.
我挺喜g他的 不^他不是外行
He's not a guy that you say, "The eighth inning is yours,
你不可能_他f "第八局就看你的了
lefties Vs. Righties."
左撇子τ移沧"
In my opinion.
@是我的看法
I don't know what Billy Beane and management understands about him.
我不知道比利.e恩和 管理邮窃觞N看他的
He only throws the ball about 82, 83 miles an hour. There must be something...
但他的投球r速只有82 83a 得有ce的…
He is a freak, and not in a good way.
他是怪胎 @可不是在F他
Let me ask you this.
我你
Talking about trying to win a diVision.
如果想在分^Y@
We're counting on DaVid to be the guy he was.
我指望大l刀未老
I haVe my doubts. He's gotten old.
但我有c岩 他已老了
That's why he's not in new York anymore, not in cleveland anymore.
所以他不在~s 也不在克利夫m 他o可去
We paid him the money we should'Ve been giVing to Johnny Damon.
我本o尼.戴蒙的X so了@U物
Hey. Jeremy Giambi.
苋鹈.吉安比
That's the one to worry about.
他才是我要心的人
He gets comps up and down Vegas more than in Oakland.
他去城的rg比在W克m更多
That should tell you something right there.
@你警醒啊
Isn't that the deal with these guys?
到底要@些砘致锇
He has one good year.
他就W光了一年
And he gets a huge offer and then he gets traded.
然後得到一PS厚的身r 接著就被D
Bob. Harder. Hatteberg.
- U勃 加力 - 哈特伯格
Good. Good.
好 很好
Billy, we haVe to talk about Hatteberg.
比利 我得哈特伯格的事
Go. There's just no feel for the spot.
- f吧 - 他在一具是]感X
I think it's a long shot that he can be a big-league first baseman.
我X得他x大盟一臼 有很L距x
It's day one of the first week. You can't judge this yet.
@才是第一周第一天 你不能就喽了
No, I think we can judge it.
不 我X得我可以喽了
I mean, I like him, you know, but I can judge him.
我喜g他 你知道 不^我是可以喽
First base is the moon to him.
一λ碚fb不可及
It wasn't to Giambi. Giambi's the worst first baseman in baseball.
吉安比就]被看臭啊 吉安比初是最差的一臼至
Gonna compare him to Giambi? What are we talking about?
- 你拿他跟吉安比比 - f什N呢
All right.
好吧
What do you think, Wash?
你X得呢 A叔
The nice way to say it is he lacks confidence.
f好c是他缺乏自信
Well, give him some.
那就o他自信
I'll do that, but we got Pena, who can play first.
我的 不^我有佩{ 他能打一
And he's looking mighty good out there.
而且他B很好
We wanna go with Hattie.
就用哈特
We got six weeks.
有六周rg
Get down in it.
用心c
There you go. Scotty H.
- 很好 - 斯科特.H
That's what I'm talking about. Picking machine.
- 就是@ - 烨蚝檬职
It's only baseball.
就是棒球而已
This better work.
@事最好行得通
I'm just kidding you.
逗你的啦
Let's go, Oakland!
上啊 W克m
What is wrong with this thing? It's a dollar, man.
- @|西怎N回事 - 要一美元 哥
What? Welcome to Oakland, D.J.
- 什N - g迎W克m D.J
Oh, you gotta be shitting me.
真是搞笑
I think this year, we're gonna show that it takes a team to win,
我想今年的比 C明F才倮
not any individual guy, just a team.
而不是靠某人 是F
And I think we got a hell of a ball club here.
我X得我很
Chad, are you intimidated at all today?
查德 你今天X得有毫
I wouldn't say I'm intimidated, really. I'm just really excited, like you said.
不能f有毫 真的 我就是挺d^的 就像你f的
Jeremy, how's the team gonna fare without your brother, Jason?
苋鹈.吉安比 ]有了你哥哥苌 @支球要如何取
Well, you know, the organization did a great job
就目前碚f 球找到了新人填a空缺
of bringing in good young guys to fill that role.
做得挺成功的
Let's face it, they're getting a deal with you.
f \蛹沂潜阋rI到的你
The Yankees are paying Jason a lot of money.
洋基s高rI了苌
You are coming here on a dime. How does that make you feel?
你在@Y的酬谥挥心屈Nc 你感受怎
I feel good. Um...
我感X很好 呃...
How are the nerves in your fingers? You know.
- 你手指的情r如何 - 就那
Gotta start with the age, 36 years old.
我ff年g吧 你36q了
How do you think your body's gonna hold up?
你X得自己的身w 能芜^一季
You spend a lot of time at strip clubs, partying.
你在衣舞吧和狂g上花了大把rg
Do you resent the attention you get off the field?
你υ鱿率艿降年P注X得琅
I love it.
不啊 我喜g
You spend a lot of time in Vegas. I do.
- 你常在城打混 - 是的
I feel great. I did a lot of work to get... Excuse me. Get out of my shot.
- 我感X很好 就像我f的 做了很多洹 - 抱歉 你e踔我的R^
Sorry, go ahead.
抱歉 f
There have been questions about my age
於我的年g
and my declining skills, some say, but I'm here to prove that wrong.
和所^的技能下滑 你有很多疑 不^我C明自己的
I asked if you were 100 percent.
我是你百分百_定
Excuse me, Mr. Beane? Hey, Chad.
- 抱歉 e恩先生 - 嗨 查德
Hey, I'm not disturbing you, am I? Not at all. What's up?
- 我]打_你吧 - ]有 怎N了
I wanted to say thank you for this opportunity.
我想感x你o我@C
Well, we enjoy having you. It's gonna work out well for all of us.
很高d你能成槲的T 我都@益匪\的
I appreciate it, sir. Nobody's ever given me a chance like this before.
我很感激 先生 ]人o我打大盟的C
Nobody?
]有?
Well, just you, sir.
只有你 先生
Well, it's a big day, one you won't forget.
噢 @成榇笕兆 你永h不忘的
Appreciate it. And I wanna let you know
非常感x 我就想f
I'm gonna be praying for you and your family.
我槟愫湍愕募胰似矶\
No problem.
好的
Well, here we are just minutes away from the season opener of 2002
F在xW克m\蛹谊 2002年的_只剩追昼
The first pitch is moments away.
第一局比即㈤_始
We'll come back with the national anthem.
奏歌r我再回
Opening day is upon us.
e走_ 今天就是_幕日
All right, fellas, smile. Here we go.
- 好了 夥 茄子 - 好了
I'm going in. Text me the play-by-play.
我M去了 比情用短信告V我
What? Why?
什N 槭颤N
I don't watch the games.
我不看比
Detail, halt!
小 立定
That's the third Ranger batter to be hit today.
@是德州游T兵今天第三支安打
Twice Alex Rodriguez was nicked. The ninth...
因阿v克斯._德Y格斯失` 已G煞至 第九…
I should've made you a bigger part of the conversation from day one.
囊婚_始我就J真和你
It'd be clear what we're trying to do.
你就更清楚我的
That was my mistake, Art. I take responsibility for that.
@是我的e 艾特 @是我的任
What are you trying to say?
你想f什N
Doesn't matter what moves I make if you don't play the team the way they're designed to be.
我要f 如果你不按用人 我怎N安排都]用
Billy, you're out of your depth.
比利 @你管不著
Why not Hatteberg at first? Because he can't play first.
- 槭颤N哈特伯格不在一 - 因樗守不了一
How do you know? Not my first baseball game.
- 你怎N知道 - @又不是我指У牡谝霰荣
Scott Hatteberg can't hit. He gets on base.
- 斯科特.哈特伯格不能打 - 他能上
Still keeps us in the plus column. We need to be seven over.500.
ξ碚f依然利多於弊 再A7 我的俾示统^五成了
What?
怎
Anything else?
有什N事
Yeah. I would've rather seen Bradford in the end than Magnante.
有最後一局我想看到布拉德福投球 而不是格{迪
Bradford's a righty.
布拉福德是右手投手
I don't care about righty-lefty. I do.
- 我不在乎他左是右 - 我在乎
Could this be about your contract? No.
- @是因槟愕暮贤 - 不是
This is about you doing your job and me doing mine.
@有P你做你的事 我M我的
Mine's me being left alone
我的任是全н@支
to manage this team you assembled for me.
你o我M建的球
I didn't assemble them for you, Art. No shit.
- 我不是槟憬M建的 - @然不是
Good meeting.
愉快
Every time we talk,
每次我聊完
I'm reinvigorated by my love of the game.
我@棒球的嵫都油然重生
We got Grady Fuson, former head of scouting with the Athletics.
我M到了格雷迪.富森 \蛹谊前首席球探
And, Grady, can you interpret for us what's going on?
格雷迪 你能o我解下F在的情r
They call it Moneyball. Moneyball?
- 他Q之槟球 - 魔球?
Yes, and it was a nice theory, and now it's just not working out.
@是很好的理 但就是]起作用
Billy Beane has built this team on the ideas of a guy, Bill James,
比利.e恩M建的@支伍是基於 一叫比.詹姆斯的人建的理
who wrote an interesting book on baseball statistics.
他了一本有趣的 P於棒球yW的
The problem is that Bill James never played, never managed.
}是比.山姆斯奈创蜻^球 也]管理^棒球
He was in fact a security guard at a pork-and-beans company.
其他只是一家i肉大豆公司的保安
Do you see this as a decimation of the organization?
你X得@是球的末日了
He bought a ticket on the Titanic.
我X得他是自に缆
Oh, boy.
天啊
He's tried to come up with a new approach.
他想找新的突破
My hat's off to him. It won't work.
我λ表示尊敬 但@行不通
One-two pitch. Tejada strikes out.
珊靡 塔哈_三振出局
And that is the game.
比Y束
The Seattle Mariners win both games on this series, Ray.
西雅D水手龆稼A了 雷
They'Ve won 10 in a row. Seattle is 13 and 3.
他BmA了10 目前西雅D133
I can't watch this shit.
看不下去了
Go on the road with the team.
你跟T一起上路比
You don't go on the road with the team.
你]有跟他比呢
That's why I want you to do it. Why don't you?
- 所以叫你去 - 你槭颤N不去
I can't develop personal relationships with these guys.
我不能跟他有私人情x
I gotta be able to trade them, send them down,
@硬拍芎菹滦戆阉u了
sometimes cut them.
甚至解雇
Which is something you should learn to do, by the way.
@你也得WW
I would never have to cut a player, unless you...
我永h不解雇T啊 除非你…
Oh, come on. "Come on" what?
- 拜 - 拜什N啊
Let's practice. No.
- 我下 - 不干
Yeah. I'm a player. You gotta cut me from the roster.
就要 我是球T 你要解雇我
No. Go.
- 不 - 快
What do you mean, no? No.
- 你f什N不啊 - 不
Do it. This is stupid.
- 快c - @太蠢了
Part of the job, man.
@是工作的一部分 夥
Fine.
好吧
Billy, please have a seat. I need to talk to you for a minute.
比利 坐 我要和你
Go on.
^m
You've been a huge part of this team.
你一直是Y的重要成T
But sometimes you have to make decisions for the team.
但有r你必要槿著想
I'm sure you can understand.
我想你懂的
You're cutting me? I'm really sorry.
- 你要解雇我? - 非常抱歉
I just bought a house here.
我在@YI了房子
Well... In Oakland.
- 呃 - 就在W克m
Well, uh... Well...
唔 呃…
"Well... Well..."? That's all you got to say?
"呃... 呃..." 你就f得出@
My kid just started a new school.
我的孩子M入新W校
They made friends. That's, uh...
- 他交到朋友 - 那…
You shouldn't pull them out in the middle of the year.
你不要在W期中打嗨
You should wait. What the hell are you talking about?
- 你等等 - 你在f些什N鬼啊
I don't know. I shouldn't have...
我不知道 我]法…
I'm not gonna do this. I think this is stupid.
我不@N做的 我X得@太傻了
I'm not gonna fire anybody, and this is dumb.
我不_除任何人 @太傻了
They're professional ballplayers. Just be straight with them.
他是I球T 直接告V他就是
No fluff, just facts.
不要f扯 就f事
Pete, I gotta let you go. Jack's office will handle the details.
皮特 我得你x_ 芸说霓k公室
That's it? Pfft.
- 就@? - 卡
Really?
真的
You rather get a bullet to the head or five to the chest and bleed to death?
你是想X袋直接中 是胸口中五流血致死?
Are those my only two options?
只有@x癜
Go on the road with the team.
跟球出去比吧
Okay.
好吧
Say, bro.
喂 夥
Let me ask you a question. Yeah.
- 你} - 好的
How come your boss doesn't travel with the team?
你老怎N不跟球一起出T
He doesn't like to mingle with the players.
他不喜g跟球T打成一片
Is that supposed to make us easier to cut?
是榱碎_除我r不擂
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道 我不清楚
And how come soda is a dollar in the clubhouse?
有 槭颤N俱凡垦Y的汽水 要付一美元
I never seen nothing like that.
我]^@N事
Billy likes to keep the money on the field.
比利想把X花在球錾
Soda money?
省汽水那cX
Really?
真的
Where on the field is the dollar I'm paying for soda?
我I汽水的一美元在球龅氖颤N地方呢
It's hard to see exactly,
@是很yf清楚
but it's there, yeah. Yeah, it is hard to see.
- 不^的_在那呢 - 嗯 是很y看到
I'm done.
我]事了
Hey, Dad. Hi, honey.
- 嘿 老爸 - 嗨 H鄣
How are you? I'm good.
- 你好 - 很好
Was it bumpy? It was okay.
- 中途簸 - 好啦
So with this loss tonight, the Oakland Athletics
加上今晚的失 W克m\蛹谊
incredibly, haVe lost 14 of their last 17 games.
在17霰荣Y掉了14 y以置信
They are 10 games back in the American League West.
在美西^已落後^名10俨
Is it fair to say the experiment has failed?
可以f失×
Well, absolutely. It was predictable.
然 @早可A的
You don't wish anybody a lack of success, but the facts are in front of you.
]人希望e人失 但事[在眼前
You can't blame Art Howe.
@不能怪艾特.哈
No.
是的
The fact of the matter is, this is not about statistics, this is about people.
F就是 @跟y]PS @是人的比
Art Howe is not the problem.
艾特.哈不是}
The problem is in the general manager's office with Billy Beane.
- 大失 - }是理室Y的比利.e恩
The root of the problem for me is philosophical.
在我看 }的根源很明晰
I said it before. This is fantasy baseball.
我之前就f了 那是想像中的棒球
Billy is just not thinking.
比利完全]^大X思考
Start thinking about a new GM, making changes.
考]Q新理 做c改
He never goes to the games.
他聿豢幢荣
This was Very predictable.
@Y果@而易
He needs to look at what's going on.
他看看錾系那r
The man needs to get real. I want Billy Beane gone.
- 他J真起砹 - 我要比利.e恩下台
Calling for Beane's head. I want your thoughts.
e恩的X袋 有人找 你到底在想什N
The past 18 games, they'Ve been shut out or scored one run four times.
之前的18霰荣Y 有4霰煌攴饣蛑坏1分
They're just not scoring enough.
他得分太低了
It's not just the offense, not Thad Bosley and the hitters.
不光是打暨M攻的} 不是_德.波士力（教）和打者的}
It's everything. If there was one thing you could pick out, you'd try to fix it,
一切都有} 如果只是某} 可以Da救
but just everything is in a funk right now.
但@支完全陷入低潮
What the hell am I doing?
我到底在做什N
Oh, man.
天啊
Look, Steve.
你看 史蒂夫
I believe in what we're doing.
我ξ在做的事很有信心
The record doesn't reflect the strength of this team
我X得不能反映 @支伍的力
or where we're gonna be at the end of the season.
也不代表季末我能@得的成
Now, Pete and I here feel very strongly that we stay on the track we've chosen.
我和皮特都孕 我要^m猿衷淼姆结
Our sample size has been too small. It's too...
我之前的颖不 @…
Early. It's still early.
早 下定早
Where do we expect to be by the All-Star break?
到全明星停期前 我A期可以到什N水平
Our goal and our expectation
我的目撕臀的A期
is by mid-July to be within seven games of first.
是到7月中和^名的俨钤7鲆
That would be this working.
一切有好D
That keeps us in the hunt. Exceptionally well.
- 到r我有Cs上 - 好得出乎意料
By July. July.
- 到7月 - 7月
And what's gonna prevent you from accomplishing that?
那有什N阻K你 _成那目说
What are you afraid of?
你在心什N
Nothing. That's why we're here, Steve.
]有 所以我才在@Y 史蒂夫
That's why we get up in the morning. That's all we do.
那就是我每天忙活的事 我一直在努力的
More? Yeah, a little more.
- 再睃c? -  再多c
Don't tell your mother. I won't.
- e告V - 不的
Chocolate sauce? Yes.
- 巧克力u? - 好
Stop.
蛄
Big spoon or little spoon? Little spoon.
- 要大勺子是小勺子 - 小的
Thank you.
xx
Dad, there's no way you're gonna lose your job, right?
爸 你不G了工作吧
What?
什N
Well, I don't know.
]有啦
I'm just wondering. Where'd you hear that?
- 我就是想想… - 你哪穆淼
Well, I go on the Internet sometimes.
我有r上W
Well, don't do that. Don't go on the Internet.
不要 e上W
Or watch TV or read newspapers
e看新 e看蠹
or talk to people.
或是e人瞎f
I don't talk to people. I just read stuff.
我不跟人聊天 就是看c|西
Honey, everything's fine. Everything's fine.
H鄣 一切都很好 ]}的
Really, you don't have to worry.
真的 你不用心
But if you lose your job, will you have to move away?
但如果你G了工作 你不是得搬走了?
Honey, I'm not gonna lose my job.
甜心 我不G了工作的
You don't have to worry.
你e心
Okay. Hey.
- 好的 - 喂
There's no problem. Okay.
- ]}的 - 好的
All right? I got uptown problems, which are not problems at all.
好 我有一堆麻 但都不是}
You're not worried, right?
你不心 是吧
No, I'm not worried. Okay.
- 我]心 - 好
Pena.
是佩{
Okay.
好吧
I want Dye in right,
我要戴守右外野
Justice DH'ing, Pena on the bench,
Z斯蒂斯指定代打 佩{後a
Hatteberg at first,
哈特伯格守一
and anyone but Mags first out of the pen.
要格作槭装l投手
You want Pena on the bench?
你要佩{坐板凳？
That's right. So you can play Hattie.
正是 @幽悴拍苡霉特
Pena is not only the best first baseman,
佩{不H是Y最好的一臼
he's the only first baseman.
而且是我唯一的一臼
Hattie gets on base more than Pena.
哈特上韭时扰寮{高多了
In fact, 20 percent more. And his fielding?
- H上是高20% - 但他的守淠
His fielding does not matter.
他的防守oPo要
I've heard enough of this. Have you?
- @我得蚨嗔 - 是
And I, uh...
而且我…
I disagree with you, plain and simple.
握f 我不同意
And moreover, I'm playing my team
有 我@ш
in a way that I can explain in job interviews next winter.
明年冬天述的r候才f得清楚
Okay? Ahem.
好了
Hattie. Not Pena.
用哈特 不要佩{
How you doing? Good, how you doing, man?
- 你怎 - 很好 你呢
Get some sleep last night?
昨晚睡得好
As the A 's hit the field, we are ready for baseball.
\蛹谊上隽 溟_始比
First one out of the dugout is rookie sensation carlos Pena,
第一走出休息^的 是新星卡洛斯.佩{
one of the few bright lights in this lineup, taking his spot at first base.
本x手Y稀有的希望 他站到了一疚恢蒙
Billy, quick question. Do you expect these guys to produce more or...?
比利 一小} 你是否期望@些T有更好的…
Not now. What's the reason for the slump?
- F在不行 夥 - 成暴跌的原因是什N
Get down.
下
Is losing fun?
球很有趣
Is losing fun? No.
- 球很有趣 - 不
What are you having fun for?
那你在な颤N纷
That's what losing sounds like.
@起聿畔褫球
Are you okay, Dad?
你]事吧 爸爸
You're doing it again. What?
- 你又砹 - 什N
You're worrying about me.
你在心我
You're in last place, Dad.
你|底了 爸爸
Do I look worried? Yeah.
- 我看起n] -
Because you're getting on an airplane, and those things crash all the time.
那是因槟阋坐wC @|西常往下掉
Please stop worrying about your dad.
不要操心你老爹了
We're all set. Okay.
- 都安排好了 - 好
I love you. Love you too.
- 我勰 - 我也勰
All right. Your dad's not in trouble.
好了 你爸爸]}
Okay.
好啦
Yeah.
好吧
Suzanne, get me Ed Wade. Okay.
- K珊 o我M艾德.f德（M城M城人理） - 好
Coffee on? Yes.
- 咖啡好了 - 是的
Good morning. Good morning, Billy.
- 早上好 - 早上好 比利
Oh, hi, Louisa.
嗨 路易莎
I need Ed Wade for Billy Beane. Hi.
- 比利.e恩想c艾德.f德通 - 嗨
Please hold.
稍候
What's up? Wade's on 2.
- 什N事啊 - f德在2
Ed? Hello?
- 艾德 - 喂
Ed, it's Billy. Billy, what's up?
- 艾德 是我比利 - 比利 怎N了
Look, I need a little help on defense. Okay.
- 著 我需要找防守球T - 好的
I'm willing to trade Jeremy Giambi for it.
我意用苋鹈.吉安比斫Q
Really? What?
- 真的 - 什N
Mm-hm. Who you got? What?
嗯 你手^有l
Well, let me think. What are you doing?
- 我想想 - 你致
Cleaning house.
清理T
Mabry? Maybe what?
- 梅布利怎 - 或S怎
No, Mabry. Hold on.
- 我是f梅布利 - 稍等
No. Why not?
- 不行 - 槭颤N
Because you can't trade Jeremy Giambi.
你不能u掉苋鹈.吉安比
He'll be fine, Ed.
就他了 艾德
Why do I get the feeling you're picking my pocket?
槭颤N我X得你在孜冶阋
I'm not. You're picking mine. Giambi's name alone is worth more.
我]有 你才孜冶阋 光吉安比@名字都值更多
What's wrong with him? Nothing.
- 他有什N} - 他]}
Can we say it's done in theory and start drawing up the paperwork?
所以@算是f好了 _始做文件了?
Okay, but you're gonna haVe... Great.
- 好吧 不^你得… - 好O了
He was gonna say something else.
他想f
When you get the answer you're looking for, hang up.
得到想要的回答就祀
Suzanne. Yes?
- K珊 - 在
David Dombrowski. Okay.
- 接大l.|布_夫斯基（底特律老虎） - 好
And Pena's going too. I don't think you should do that.
- 佩{也得走 - 我X得你不能@N做
I really don't think you should do that.
我真的X得你不能@
I want Hatteberg in the lineup tonight.
我要哈特伯格今晚就上
You need to take a minute.
比利 我想你等一等
I think you seriously need to think about what you're doing.
我真的X得你要想清楚在做什N
Because you're upset. Okay.
- 因槟愫懿凰 - 好吧
What am I missing?
我有什N]想到的
These are hard moves to explain to people.
@些Q定很y向人交待
Why is that a problem, Pete?
有} 皮特
Don't make an emotional decision, Billy.
e意庥檬 比利
David Dombrowski's on 3.
大l.|布_夫斯基在3
Look, we're gonna shake things up.
著 我要做就做Q了
Dave. Pena's going on the block. You're my first call.
大l 佩{要公_出售了 我第一通知你
Because he's making the rest of the team look bad.
因樗本其他人@得很蠢
He's gonna be a Rookie of the Year.
他得今年的新人哦
Probably an All-Star. He's an All-Star, Dave.
- f不定可以入x全明星容 - 他M全明星 大l
No. I want a reliever and cash.
不 我要後援投手加F金
Okay. You got five minutes, Dave. I'm not waiting.
好吧 o你5分 大l ^r不候
Billy, Pena is an All-Star, okay?
比利 佩{是全明星的料啊
And if you dump him and this Hatteberg thing doesn't work out, you know this is...
如果你u掉他 而哈特伯格 @招又]成功 你知道@…
This is the kind of decision that gets you fired.
@NQ定足以你G掉工作
It is.
真的
Yes, you're right.
你f的
I may lose my job.
我可能G掉工作
In which case I'm a 44-year-old guy with a high school diploma
而我44q的人 只有高中文{
and a daughter I'd like to be able to send to college.
我想送我女鹤x大W
You're 25 years old, with a degree from Yale
你25q 有耶Wv
and a pretty impressive apprenticeship.
有很棒的工作
I don't think we're asking the right question.
我K]有核心}
I think the question we should be asking is,
我想我的是
do you believe in this thing or not?
你相信我的x
I do.
我信
It's a problem you think we need to explain ourselves.
你X得我需要 向e人解的就e了
Don't. To anyone.
不解 oφl
Okay.
明白
Now, I'm gonna see this thing through, for better or worse.
我要猿值降琢 oY局好
Just tell me, do you project we'll win more with Hatteberg or Pena at first?
你只要告V我 你分析一臼怯 哈特伯格更有偎 是佩{
It's close...
Y果很接近…
but theoretically, Hatteberg.
不^理上哈特伯格更好
What are we talking about, then?
那我U什N
Dombrowski's on again, on 3.
|布_夫斯基又打砹 在3
Yeah?
喂
Okay, that'll work.
好 可以
Great. I need one more thing.
很好 有一件事
Soda. Yeah, I don't want my guys paying for soda.
汽水  我不想自己的球T再 花XI汽水
I want you to stock my machine for three years.
我要你o我的汽水Ca三年
I'm serious.
我是J真的
Great. It's a deal.
好O了 f定了
Go tell Pena he's gotta pack.
去告V佩{ 他打包走人
You want me to tell Pena? Part of the job.
- 你要我去告V佩{ - @是工作的一部分
What about Giambi? You want me to tell him too?
吉安比呢 也要我去f
I'll tell him.
我
Excuse me, Carlos? Yeah?
- 打_下 卡洛斯 - 什N事
Can I speak with you a minute? Yeah.
- 我能和你删 - 好的
Carlos, you've been traded to the Tigers.
卡洛斯 你被D到底特律老虎了
This is Jay Palmer's number.
@是.帕的
He's the traveling secretary for the team.
他是球的差旅管理秘
He's expecting your call. He'll take care of everything.
他正等你的 他理其他一切事宜
Is that it? Yes.
- 就@恿? -
Okay.
好吧
Art, you got a minute?
艾特 你F在有空
Yeah. Take a seat.
嗯 坐吧
You can't start Pena at first tonight. You'll have to start Hatteberg.
今晚你不能首l佩{上一玖 你要用哈特伯格
I don't wanna go 15 rounds, Billy.
我不想再扯@} 比利
The lineup card is mine, and that's all.
M容的是我 U少f
That lineup card is definitely yours.
然 M容的是你
I'm just saying you can't start Pena at first.
我只是f一静荒苡门寮{了
Well...
哦
I am starting him at first.
我就要他去一
I don't think so. He plays for Detroit now.
我想不行了 他F在榈滋芈尚Яα
You traded Pena?
你Q走了佩{？
Yeah.
]e
And Menechino, Hiljus, Tam are all being sent down.
有曼{奇Z 希吉斯 塔姆被解聘了
You are outside your mind. Yeah. Cuckoo.
- 你了 - 是哦 我是子
You wanted to see me? Yeah, Jeremy, grab a seat.
- 你想我? -  苋鹈 坐吧
Jeremy, you've been traded to the Phillies.
苋鹈 我把你Q到M城人了
This is Ed Wade's number. He's a good guy, the GM.
@是艾德.f德的 他是球理 是好人
He's expecting your call.
你o他打吧
Buddy will help you with the plane flight.
布德湍阌wC
You're a good ballplayer, Jeremy,
你是好球T 苋鹈
and we wish you the best.
祝你好\
Jeremy's gone too.
苋鹈滓沧吡
You're killing this team.
你要Я诉@球
Art, I can do this all day long.
艾特 我可以一直@N做下去
Hey.
嘿
You agree with this?
你Υ撕oh?
Hundred percent.
z毫]有
You want this door closed?
想要P上T
Scotty H. Sir?
- 斯科特.H - 是的 先生?
Go field some grounders. Yes, sir.
- 去接L地球吧 - 好的
Everybody, listen up.
大家好了
You may not look like a winning team...
也S你看起聿幌窆谲
but you are one.
但你就是
So...
所以...
play like one tonight.
今晚打出冠幼
Oh, shit.
要命了
When you're getting your pitch, you're hitting.625, massive.
舻侥阆g的球r 你的打袈适.625 相@人啊
You're crushing the ball.
你能把球打爆
But when you swing at things... Your pitch is middle-in.
但你y]...不挑你擅L冉钦中球r
When you're swinging low and away, you're batting.158.
而是]棒舻氖堑忘c外角球 你的打袈手挥.158
Every at bat's like a hand of blackjack.
每打刀枷21c的一牌
Every card that's dealt, your odds change.
每l完一牌 局荻伎赡芊P
So every first-pitch strike, your batting average goes down about 75 points.
所以一旦第一好球]糁 你的羟蚵示拖陆75c
Seventy-five points.
75c啊
He should throw 100 pitches before the fifth.
Ψ酵妒在第五局前投出100球
You wanna knock that starter out.
你得把首l投手o累趴下 他在牛棚Y起不
I want you taking at bats off the 10th and 11 th pitcher by the end.
我要你在系列收Pr氖 甚至11投手那拿足打
This is your basic breakdown of the pitches,
@Y的y分析@示了
where you should be hitting them, why.
你的所有理想羟螯c 以及原因
So you want us to walk more? Good question. Yes.
- 所以你是要我更多得被保送 - 得好 是的
Mr. Justice.
Z斯蒂斯先生
Had a few thoughts. Yeah?
- 我有些想法 - 是
Yeah. Gonna teach me some things?
- 是的 - 想教我什N
Excuse me?
什N
Never seen a GM talk to players like that.
]^理 那痈球Tv
You never seen a GM who was a player.
你也]^^球T的理吧
Huh.
哈
We got a problem, David? No, it's okay.
- 有什N} 大l - 不 ]什N
I know your routine.
我知道你的套路
It's patter. It's for effect.
@是碥的 榱诉_到效果
But it's for them, all right? That shit ain't for me.
但@一套λ好用 ξ]用
Oh, you're special?
那你很特殊咯
You're paying me 7 million bucks a year, man, so, yeah,
你每年o我700f美元 所以 是的
maybe I am, a little bit.
也S我是有c特e
No, man, I ain't paying you 7.
不 夥 我]o你700f
Yankees are paying half your salary.
洋基了你一半薪水
That's what the New York Yankees think of you.
@就是~s洋基δ愕B度
They're paying you $3.5 million to play against them.
他o你350f美元 你碜鏊的κ
Where you going with this, Billy?
你到底想f什N 比利
David, you're 37.
大l 你37q了
How about you and I be honest about what each of us want out of this?
不如我坦白c ff彼此想要什N
I wanna milk the last ounce of baseball you got in you.
我要榨干你最後一滴棒球能力
And you wanna stay in the show.
而你想留在錾
Let's do that.
我合作吧
I'm not paying you for the player you used to be.
我不是槟阍的x煌o你X
I'm paying you for the player you are right now.
而就是看上F在的你
You're smart. You get what we're trying to do here.
你很明 你明白我想做什N
Make an example for the younger guys.
o年p人做榜影
Be a leader.
Iд
Can you do that?
你能做到
All right. I got you.
好吧 我知道了
We're cool?
我之g]}了吧
We're cool.
]}
Scotty H.
斯科特.H
Yo, what's up, D. J? Picking machine.
- 你好 D.J. - 烨C器哈
How you liking first base, man?
喜g一 夥
It's coming along. Picking it up.
有M展吧 ^m烨虬
You know, tough transition, but I'm starting to feel better with it.
你知道 D很困y 不^我感X越碓胶昧
Yeah? Yeah.
- 是 - 嗯
What's your biggest fear?
你最怕什N
A baseball being hit in my general direction.
任何朝我w淼陌羟
That's funny. Seriously, what is it?
很好笑 f真的 是什N
No, seriously, that is.
真的 就是@
Well, hey, good luck with that.
嘿 那祝你好\啊
Be social out there.
要多社交啊
Social. Social. Like a greeter at the Gap.
- 社交 - 社交 就像GAP的迎eT
Guy steps into your office, chat him up.
有人跑到你的地P 就和他聊聊
You're well-read. You went to school.
你x^ 上^W
Yeah. Have some fun. Relax.
-  - _心c 放
Everyone wants to attack. Quit trying to attack.
每人都想M攻 不要老想M攻
Let the game come to you, man. There's no clock on this thing.
比跟著你的奏走 @|西不限rg的
This is a war of attrition.
@是消耗
If I take more, I could even take a few strikes, but I'll get walked more.
我可以多放^c球 甚至放^好球 被保送上镜茁室苍酱
You get on base, we win. You don't, we lose.
只要上 我就A 上不了 我就
And I hate losing, Chavvie. I hate it.
我球 查威 我
I hate losing more than I even wanna win.
比起想A 我更
And there's a difference.
@是有^e的
No bunts. Bunts is an out.
- 不要|舳檀 - 短打就意味著一人出局
Even if the third baseman is back? No bunting whatsoever.
- 就算三臼轴嵬艘膊恍 - 不管怎右膊灰短打
If someone bunts on us, throw it to first.
如果Ψ奚短打 直接烨蛉咏o一
Don't be a hero and go to second.
e逞英雄了想p
Let them make the mistakes.
等著橙朔稿e`
When your enemy's making mistakes, don't interrupt them.
你橙朔稿er ^Σ灰打_他
They're giving you an out. Just giving it to you.
他是在o你C 你踢他出局
Take it. Say thank you.
抓住C 道x就好
Another thing. No more stealing.
有一件事 不要I
That's what I do, what you pay me to do.
但我就擅LI 你雇我砭褪亲我I
I pay you to get on first, not get thrown out at second.
我雇你榱苏旧弦 不是榱吮唤⒃诙
This is a process. It's a process, it's a process. Okay?
@是^程 ^程 知道
Jason takes it, goes to second for the only out, and the A 's get a run.
苌（洋基的吉安比）接住球 扔o二 一出局 \蛹谊得一分
Jermaine Dye homers again, his second in two games.
苓~恩.戴又一支全敬 @是他霰荣中的第二支了
And the A 's are still hanging in. We'll get you scores here.
\蛹谊在猿 @Y是目前的e分 （2002年6月6日）
The A 's pull within two of the Angels for the wild-card chase.
\蛹谊和天使的俨畋焕近了 只差2鼍湍苡CZ外卡
The Reds haVe now dropped fiVe in a row
tmF在已B5
as Oakland beats them in the beginning of this series 5 to 3.
在@鱿盗匈一_始就被W克m 以5比3I先
Tejada walks.
塔哈_被保送了
Ball four.
四那
Ball four and Hatteberg walks.
四那 哈特伯格被保送上
What is happening in Oakland? The A 's haVe won seven in a row.
W克ml生什N了 \蛹谊已BmA了7
A lot of excitement. What a winning streak.
真是令人d^ @是萑绯卑
But how about the calming influence of Art Howe?
不是艾特.哈住了心
When you say "your source," if it's not me or Peter, they don't know.
如果不是指我或者皮特 那你指的消息碓淳屯耆不知所^
He's managing an unorthodox team.
他ьI著一不同こ５年伍
Right. It's not a perfect roster.
-  - @容K不出色
But right now, Art Howe is the reason this team is winning.
但F在艾特.哈才是 @支伍倮的原因
He deserves the credit. Great, thanks. Bye.
- 他值得@拥陌 - 好 xx 再
Did you hear that?
你了
I heard "seven in a row." You get the Cleveland matchups?
我到"BmA了7" 你拿到克利夫m的攻防名瘟
Yeah, right here.
就在@Y
Voos. Billy.
- 布斯 - 比利
That smell is getting worse. I'm on it.
- @Y的味道更y了 - 我@就理
What are we doing? Splitting it in half?
- 今晚怎N打算 - 各半怎N
Both sides of the plate. Got it.
- 左右蛇都要 - 好的
Huddy. Mix it up. Yes, sir.
- 赫迪 得Q球路 - 好的 先生
Trust your slider, yeah? Yes, sir.
- 相信你的旋D球 - 好的
You guys quit distracting him.
你e再他分心了
You couldn't hit that shit last night with a paddle.
你昨晚不急著打那些球啊
You gotta see more pitches.
多等浊蚵
All right, Billy. Patience.
- 好的 比利 - 要有耐心
Hey, David. Hey, Billy.
- 嘿 大l - 嘿 比利
Great at bats. Thank you.
- 打得好 - xx
Really quality. Thank you.
很有|量
Base hit to right field. Tejada scores.
右外野安打 塔哈_得分
ChaVez coming in. The ball gets past Guiel.
查f斯也跑回本玖 球w^了w
The A 's, from 5-nothing down, now lead 6 to 5.
\蛹谊以5比0落後 反超6比5I先
The Oakland A 's are completely out of hand at the moment.
F在W克m\蛹谊直是\野R
They also took back-to-back series at Boston and at new York.
他在波士D和~s也接B@
Remember when they traded Jeremy Giambi in June
得六月r他苋鹈.吉安比 uoM城人
and everyone thought they'd just giVen up?
所有人都J樗放了
Actually, not so much.
其正相反
Suzanne, get Shapiro on the phone.
2002 球T交易截止日
You thinking Rincon? His season's done. He's lost faith.
- 你想要林康? -  他的季Y束了 他]信心了
I think he's gonna dump him. Hard-core.
- 我想R克他 - 猜得妙啊
Shapiro on 2.
史派_在2
Mark, Billy. Let's be honest.
R克 是我比利 我_T山吧
A premier setup man isn't gonna get you closer to the play-offs.
靠一秀的後援投手是不可能 湍阙A得季後的
Are you referring to Rincon?
你是指林康
He's a luxury you can't afford, man.
夥 你可不起@奢侈品
And you can? There's half a million on his contract.
你能 他合同上要付50f
And we'Ve got at least one other suitor.
而且要I他的人不止一啊
By "at least one," you mean one.
"不止一"就是只有一吧
Who is it? I'd rather not say.
- 是l - 我不想f
San Francisco. San Francisco.
f金山巨人
I'll call you back.
^涸俅蚪o你
What do you think we can get for Magnante?
你X得我用格{迪能Ql
Nothing.
什N也Q不了
What's left on Venafro's contract? Two seventy-five.
- f{夫_的合同上剩多少 - 27.5f
Suzanne, get me Sabean on the line.
K珊 臀医尤鲑e恩
Get the Giants interested in Venafro, Mark's only got one buyer for Rincon.
巨人d趣D到f{夫_身上 要I林康的就只剩一
Us. On 3.
- 就是我 - 他在3
Saby-Sabster, it's Billy. What do you think of Venafro?
_比 我是比利 你X得f{夫_怎
I can let you have him for almost nothing.
我半u半送o你
Why would you do that? Because I'm amazing.
- 你安的什N心呢 - 因槲沂好人
I want a couple bucks and a sweetener.
我就要cX和一附加l件
Throw in, say...
你就o我…
Anderson. Anderson.
- 安德森 - 安德森
I like Anderson. No, you don't. Nobody likes him.
- 我喜g安德森 - 你才不 ]人喜g安德森
I don't know why I'm doing this. But let's do it.
我都不知道我致镞@N做 但就@影
Venafro for Michaelson. Anderson. I don't know his name.
- f{夫_Q~克森 - 安德森 - 我是f安德森 我都不知道他叫什N
I'll think about it. Think about it and call me back.
- 我考]下 - 好好考] o我
Get Shapiro on.
接史派_
Shapiro's on 2.
史派_在2
Mark. You can't afford him, Billy.
- R克 - 你I不起他 比利
You sure about that?
你_定
I get the impression the market for Rincon is softening.
怎N我X得林康]什N市隽
Huh? I could be wrong,
- 啊? - 我可能e了
but I'd call whoever's interested
如果我是你
and see if they're still interested. Call me back.
我打o之前有d趣的人 得回我哦
What about the Mets for Venafro? You offered him to the Giants.
- 大都f{夫_有d趣 - 你把他Io巨人啊
Suzanne, Steve Phillips.
K珊 接史蒂夫.w利浦
Between Bonds, Kent, Nen, Snow, San Francisco's never gonna do it.
巨人有邦 肯特 南 史Z 才不要f{夫_
Totally agree. We just need them to cool on Rincon.
- 完全同意 - 我只是要他放林康
Phillips on 2. Steve-o, it's Billy.
- w利浦在2 - 史蒂夫 是我比利
I hear you're looking for a reliever. I can give you Venafro.
我f你想要左手後援投手 我可以o你f{夫_
I can make it quick and easy. What's the angle?
- 瘟水 - 你有啥企D
No angle. Who am I getting fleeced for?
- ]企D啊 - 那你想拐跑l
Hang on a sec. Uh, Bennett, maybe?
- 等等 - 本{特怎N
How old? Twenty-six.
- 年g - 26
Twenty-six, Double-A? Forget it.
26q 在2A（培B後涞男÷盟） 不行
Duncan, no.
肯 不行
No. Furbush, no.
不行 弗布什 不行
Eckerton? Eckerton? Eckerton.
艾肯特怎N 就
I like Eckerton. You don't even know who Eckerton is.
- 我喜g艾肯特 - 你根本都不知道他是l
Is Venafro hurt? No, he's fine, he's fine.
- f{夫_受了 - ]有 他很好
It's just an issue for us.
只是我炔坑悬c}
Last couple times, he got hammered. Not his fault.
- 之前纱 他投球都被麸w了 - 不是他的}
That was us. We misused him. It's Steve.
- 是我的} 策略e` - 是史蒂夫
I'm almost done. Steve Schott.
- 就快好了 - 史蒂夫.莎特（老）
Look, Steve-o, let me be straight with you.
- 稍等 他在打 - 著史蒂夫 我直接跟你f吧
Here's the deal. I'm getting Rincon. It's a done deal.
是@拥 我要了林康 已好了
I heard the Giants... Giants want Venafro for Michaelson.
- 但我f巨人… - 不 巨人想用~克森Qf{夫_
Anderson. I'd rather deal with you.
- 是安德森 - 我Qo你
You can give me Eckerton and $225,000 in cash,
你可以o我艾肯特和22.5fF金
and the Giants can't.
巨人什N都]有
I'll think about it. Think about it.
- 我考]一下 - 考]吧
But whoever calls me back first gets Venafro.
不^l先回我 f{夫_就wl
Schott hung up.
莎特（老）炝
Oh, I want this one.
我一定要成功
Why isn't anybody calling?
槭颤N]人打戆
Shapiro's on 2.
史派_在2
Yeah?
喂
Okay, let me talk to my owner. I'll call you back.
好 我跟老 然後回你 xx
Get Steve on the phone. Schott or Phillips?
- 接史蒂夫的 - 莎特（老）是w利浦（大都）
Why would we call Phillips? Phillips has gotta call us.
我嵋打ow利浦 是他打o我
Tell him I'm on the other line.
告V他 我在打
Hi, Mr. Schott, it's Peter Brand. I apologize for putting you on hold.
嗨 莎特先生 我是皮特.布m德 很抱歉要你等候
Billy asked me to call you back. Tell him we want 225,000 for Rincon.
- 比利叫我回你 他在打 - f我要22.5fI林康
Billy says he needs $225,000 for Ricardo Rincon.
比利f他要22.5fIY卡多.林康
Please.
你
Yes, I added the "please" at the end.
是 是我加的"你"二字
Okay. Let me... Hold on one second, please.
好吧 我...稍等一下
Tell him I'll pay for him.
告V他 我斫oX
But when I sell him back for twice the amount next year, I keep the money.
但如果明年我把他u了p倍rX 那得w我
Okay, so Billy says he'll pay for Rincon himself.
好 比利f他自己付XI林康
But when he sells him for more money next year, he's keeping the profit.
但明年如果u了高r 利都w他了
Thank you very much. We'll call you back. Thank you.
非常感x 我再打o你 xx
Come on. Come on.
戆 再
Suzanne, call Shapiro ba... Never mind, I got him right here.
K珊 打o史派_ 算了 他打砹
Mark. Yeah.
R克 是我
Listen, I don't want Rincon pitching against me tonight.
著 我可不要林康今晚跟我打μ
Tell him to change clothes and send him over. I got you the money.
告V他Q服 送他^ X浜昧
Great.
太好了
I don't wanna dampen the mood at all, but since we picked up Rincon...
我不想破夥 但我有了林康...
We gotta send someone down.
就要踢某人出局了
Mags. Hey, Billy.
- 格 - 嗨 比利
I know I've been struggling lately.
我知道最近我有c吃力
But second half of the season, definitely turn it around. Ricky and l...
但下半季一定有改善的 Y奇和我想到…
Mike, I need you to stop getting dressed.
格 不要再整b了
Traded?
我被u了?
I'm sorry for the crap news.
很抱歉Ыo你南息
I know it hurts.
我知道@很痛苦
Mike, I can't have 26 guys in the clubhouse.
格 球Y不能有26人
I get it. I get it.
我知道 我知道
Okay. Thanks.
好的 xx
Hey, Ricardo.
嘿 Y卡多
This must be a bit of a shock, I guess.
@一定你吃了一@吧
Mabry hits one deep to right-center field.
梅布利糁幸磺 球wM中右外野
Racing back, Fick can't get it.
跑者已跑回本 菲克接不到了
It bounces to the wall. One run is in. Two runs are in.
球到得分牌板上 一跑回本 跑回本
Mabry, on one pitch, has shot the A 's in front.
梅布利一球之g 就o\蛹谊眍I先
Strike three called. TwelVe straight wins for the Athletics.
三振 \蛹谊B12隽 （B伲
Man aliVe, was it hairy.
天呢 太不可思h了
Something strange is now happening in Oakland.
W克m出了怪事了
You cannot argue that point.  TwelVe straight.
- F在分o可置疑了 - B12
They're making a joke out of the American League.
他美棒球盟成了笑
They were in Detroit today...  He throws to first.
- 他今天在底特律 - 他鹘o一
And that's the sound of 14 straight Victories.
@就是14B俚g呼
Fourteen, the longest run this year.
14 @是今年的最高
It has slingshot the A 's into first in the AL West. A nice streak.
\蛹谊已攀升到美西^第一名 倮一l不可收拾
This team was written off.
@支球曾一度被o情抨
How do you explain, otherwise, the Victories they'Ve come up with?
如何解他取得的@人倮
The Oakland A 's are gonna win 16 consecutiVe games.
W克m\蛹谊A得了16鲞B
This is the longest win streak in baseball, folks, in 25 years.
@是25年戆羟蚪缱铋L的B儆 ^
The A 's haVe won 16 in a row.
\蛹谊已B16隽
We're going to 20! We're going to 20!
我要20B 20B
To haVe a winning streak of this duration, you haVe to be good,
要BmA到F在 伍一定很秀
but there's an element of randomness to it.
但@Y面也有偶然性
The 1927 Yankees, Ruth, Gehrig,
1927年的洋基 有路德 w瑞格 有⑹执蚓（o年洋基大容的昵Q）
Murderers' Row, some people still say the best team ever.
至今仍有人J槭亲秀的容
Longest winning streak for them that year? Nine.
他年最L的倮是多少 9B
You guys try to analyze it from a numbers standpoint.
你想用一系列的^c矸治鲞@事
I'm telling you, there is no explanation for what's occurring right now.
我告V你 F在l生的事 o法解
Do you haVe superstitions going on?
你是用了什N巫g
Do you do things so you keep the streak aliVe?
你做了什N才能保持B俚?
The all-time record of 20 does not seem impossible anymore.
破o的20B倏雌 K非不可能
The A 's were on page one of the New York Times.
今天\蛹谊上了~sr代sI
They are the story in sports in this entire country.
他是整家w育界的髌
Two-two pitch, here it is.
珊 看@
Swing and a miss! Struck him out! Number 17!
]棒落空 三振出局 第17
It's taken 71 years.
用71年了
The Oakland A 's haVe tied the Philadelphia A 's.
W克m\蛹谊平了M城人的o
The all-time franchise record 17 straight
空前^後的17B儆
and baseball's longest winning streak since 1953.
自1953年以 棒球史上最L的B儆
The A 's are two wins away from tying the American League record.
差 \蛹谊就能平了美了
It's gone! It's gone! Tejada wins it! Do you believe it?
w出去了 w出去了 塔哈_全敬 你能相信
Eighteen wins in a row!
B18
You could replay these 18 games a hundred times oVer.
你可以重}看那18次比100遍
And nobody wins 18 straight again.
]人能再次B18
It defies everything we know about baseball.
@覆了我Π羟蛩有的^念
The most amazing thing you could imagine
^去4天Y 大w育鲅Yl生了
happened oVer the last four days at the coliseum.
你能想像到最神奇的事
Tejada, up the middle. The A 's haVe won 19 in a row!
塔哈_ 直w中野 \蛹谊B19隽
The 1906 White Sox,
1906年的白m
the 1947 new York Yankees haVe company.
1947年的洋基 他有伴了
Nineteen in a row.
B19
The A 's haVe a date with destiny.
\蛹谊c倮有s
They're going for the all-time American League record,
他直奔美盟的而去
20 games in a row.
B20
We're going to 20! We're gonna take the AL record to 20, baby!
我要20B 我要把刷新到20B
Don't tell me the score, Pete.
e告V我分 皮特
No, Billy, it's me.
不 比利 是我
Sharon? Yeah.
- 莎 - 是的
You haVe a second? Yeah, what's up?
- 你有rg - 有 怎N了
Well, I didn't actually expect you to pick up.
我倒]想到你接起
I was gonna leaVe a message.
本硐肓口信的
Um, casey and I, we're here and watching the game at home.
P西和我 我在家正在看比
And I just wanted to say...
我想告V你
you did good, Billy.
你做得很棒 比利
We're really proud of you.
我槟泸傲
I appreciate it, Sharon.
xx 莎
Thank you. Good luck.
- xx - 祝你好\
Okay.
嗯
Oh, casey wants to talk to you. Hang on.
P西想跟你f 等等
Are you on your way to the stadium?
你正在去\龅穆飞
No, I'm on my way to Visalia to see our minor-league team.
不 我正要去S利 去看我的小盟 （附凫洞舐盟伍送後^T）
Turn around, please, Dad. No way, Jose.
- 快掉^啊 爸爸 - ]T
Turn around. Come on, Dad. Nope. Not gonna happen.
- 掉^吧 拜 老爸 - 不 不行
You're not gonna jinx it.
你不去厄\啦
I'll talk to you later, sweetheart. I love you.
回^再聊 甜心 我勰
Shit.
的
One out here in the fourth, and if you're just joining us,
第四局一人出局 如果你D到@l道
you missed a lot.
你e^了很多精彩啊
And the pitch to Raul Ibanez. Strike one.
到保_.依e尼羟 一好球
I think my recap will be simple.
我的述很
The A 's scored six in the first, one in the second, four in the third.
\蛹谊第一局得了6分 第二局1分 第三局4分
And people would be shocked if you just did that. Heh-heh-heh.
你f得@虞p巧 到的人吃@啦 哈哈哈
Eleven to nothing, the A 's do lead.
11比0 \蛹谊I先
Shit. Foul off the foot of Ibanez...
- 的 - 界外 好球…
Let's go, Oakland!
n啊 W克m
Now batting, number 2, catcher, Brent Mayne.
F在上羟 2 捕手布m特.梅恩
Oakland! Here we go, Oakland!
- W克m - 上啊 W克m
Safe.
安全上
Now batting,
F在上羟
number 18, left fielder Raul Ibanez.
18 左外野手保_.依e尼
Safe.
安全回
And the A 's now lead by a score of 11 to 3.
F在\蛹谊以11比3I先
A nice cushion, but you don't wanna giVe teams life
n下是不e 但不oκC
and let them wedge their way back in, even when you're...
不能他有翻P的C 即使I先…
Nobody out, the bases loaded.
]人出局 M
And Art Howe on the way to the mound to make a pitching change.
艾特.哈正走向投手丘 要作投球{整
And this game is still in a state
@霰荣的局面仍然可能
where it could get out of control for the Athletics.
超出\蛹谊的掌控
We're all told at some point we can no longer play the children's game.
某r刻 有人告V我 不能再玩小孩子的[
We just don't know when that's gonna be.
只是不知道是何r
Some of us are told at 18, some of us are told at 40, but we're all told.
可能是在18q 可能是在40q 但我有那r刻
Mike Sweeney with runners at first and third.
F在是克.斯S尼打 一救居腥
It's an 11-to-7 game, the A 's in front.
F在比分11比7 \蛹谊I先
Tam peering in for the sign.
塔姆等著投手手
Two out. Runners at first and third.
扇顺鼍 一三居腥
And the 3-2 deliVery.
珊萌模ㄇ狄M 下一球要N 三人出局此局Y束 要NO可能得分）
It's weird, Billy.
@太怪了比利
You wanna giVe up baseball to become a scout?
你想放打棒球 去球探？
I'm not a baseball player.
我不是棒球球手
Are you sure this is what you want?
你_定@是你想要的
The crowd is roaring. Koch is ready. One-two pitch.
人群在咆哮 肯什浜昧 珊靡
Alicea puts it in play, a looper to left field for a base hit.
阿里西打出去了 弧w到左外野 一支安打
Around third, tearing for the plate, here comes the tying run.
跑^三 直n本 平分了
Sliding safe. And the ball game is tied at 11-all.
滑境晒 p方11分平
Holy Toledo.
上帝啊
The A 's haVe blown an 11-to-nothing lead.
\蛹谊浪M了11比0的I先
This is the specter of a development that has been lurking now
自幕始谊在第四局得到5分後
ever since the fiVe-run fourth inning by the Royals.
人心^的恐慌_始蔓延了
And the A 's date with destiny is on hold right now.
\蛹谊c倮的s出F停了
Hatteberg. Hattie.
哈特伯格 哈特
Grab a bat. You're hitting for Byrnesy.
拿上球棒 你代布m{斯羟
Come on, let's go. Get yourself loose.
快c 悠 去嵘
Hitting for Eric Byrnes,
埃Y克.布m{斯代打
number 10, Scott Hatteberg.
10 斯科特.哈特伯格
In your typical A 's fashion. They want a base runner here.
按\蛹谊T常的L格 派了能上镜娜松
Scott Hatteberg is so adept at drawing walks.
斯科特.哈特伯格擅L得四那虮Ｋ
He's looking for Hatteberg to get on base,
教是想哈特伯格上
maybe bring in a pinch runner.
再Q代跑
Let's go, Oakland!
上啊 W克m
That one is gone!
球w出去了（全敬)
And it's 20 consecutiVe Victories for the Oakland Athletics
@是W克m\蛹谊 第20鲞Bm倮
on an unbelieVable night
在@不可思h的夜晚
when they lost an 11-to-nothing lead
他失去了11比0的葜後
and now they win it.
最後大@全
The crowd comes back to insane life.
人群重新陷入狂
How do you explain it?
@是不解之迷啊
Crazy. Just plain crazy.
了 完全是了
Hatteberg is mobbed at home plate.
哈特伯格在本旧媳淮蠹野
In 103 years of American League baseball,
在美棒球盟103年的v史上
the Athletics haVe accomplished what no one has before.
\蛹谊的倮前o古人
They haVe won 20 consecutiVe games.
他BmA得了20倮
It's hard not to be romantic about baseball.
你]法不凵习羟
This kind of thing, it's fun for the fans.
@N盛事 是球迷的狂g
It sells tickets and hot dogs.
票房大u 峁肥垠
Doesn't mean anything.
但毫o意x
Billy, we just won 20 games in a row.
比利 我B20霭
And what's the point?
所以呢
We just got the record.
我造了
Man, I've been doing this for...
夥 我做@行已…
Listen, man.
著 夥
I've been in this game a long time.
我在@一行的rg很L了
I'm not in it for a record, I'll tell you that.
我不是榱思o淼 告V你
I'm not in it for a ring.
我不是榱斯谲指h
That's when people get hurt.
@Nr候 有人付出代r
If we don't win the last game of the Series,
如果最後一龉谲我了
they'll dismiss us.
他照硬在意我
Billy... I know these guys.
- 比利... - 我t解@些人
I know the way they think, and they will erase us.
我知道他的想法 他抹平我的成就
And everything we've done here,
我做的一切
none of it'll matter.
λ都毫o意x
Any other team wins the World Series, good for them.
其他任何球A了冠都是件好事
They're drinking champagne, they get a ring.
他_香 @得冠戒
But if we win,
但如果我A了
on our budget, with this team...
用@拥念A算 @拥那蜿
we'll have changed the game.
我就改了一切[蛞t
And that's what I want.
@才是我要的
I want it to mean something.
我要@事留下意x
The A 's going to the play-offs with the West DiVision title.
W克m\蛹谊 е西^冠^M入季後
ForgiVe the A 's if they're not celebrating.
他未大肆c祝 @情有可原
They haVe been here before,
他之前也走到^@Y
when Oakland went up two games to none on the Yanks in the ALDS,
就在去年 \蛹谊在美季候 分^BA^洋基
and went nowhere after losing three straight.
之後s直三 |羽而w
With a win today oVer the Twins, Oakland moVes into the ALcS
今天A了p城 W克m⒃1992年後
for the first time since 1992.
第一次挺M美冠
But remember one thing.
但住一件事
Percentages hold up oVer a season, but for one game, one at bat,
整季的打袈士梢院芨 可是就一霰荣 一打而言
throw the percentages out the window.
打袈]有任何意x
What the Minnesota Twins exposed is the fact that the Oakland A 's
明尼K_p子揭露了 W克m\蛹谊的真相
were fundamentally not a sound baseball team.
他K究不是一支力酝Φ那蜿
They had a flawed concept that started with the general manager
那蜿理到智囊F都著一
and the brain trust thinking they could reinVent baseball.
e`的^念 就是他可以改棒球t
You can't approach baseball
不能用空中情w的y概念
from a statistical, bean-counting point of View.
碓棒球\
It's won on the field with fundamental play.
倮需要通^打的比才能@得
You haVe to steal, you haVe to bunt, you haVe to sacrifice.
你得I 短打 奚
You gotta get men in scoring position, and you gotta bring them in.
你得T站上得分位 再送他回
And you don't do that with a bunch of statistical gimmicks.
@不是用一堆yW的花招就能Q淼
Nobody reinVents this game.
]有人可以改[蛞t
Yeah.
是我
Due respect to the Coliseum, but this is a ballpark.
我o意小看W克m主 不^@才是真正的棒球
Yes, it is.
]e
We're gonna have some lunch in a little bit.
一阂黄鸪晕顼吧
Why don't I have some coffee sent up?
我潼c咖啡
Thank you, Denise.
xx你 丹尼斯
Thanks. You're welcome.
- xx - ]PS
You know, it's her birthday and I need to get her a present,
你知道 她生日到了 我送她生日Y物
but she's usually the one that does that for me.
但通常她才是臀姨舳Y物的人
So do you have any ideas?
你有什N提h
Scarf.
巾
You mean like wool?
你是f羊毛的?
No, I meant what women wear with... You know, decorative.
不 我是指女人用作品的那N
Ah. And where would I get something like that?
啊 我到哪喝ベI@啊
No disrespect, I just lost in five for the second year in a row.
我不想失Y 但我已Bm赡贻掉分^
Get her a bowling ball for all I care.
我只想送她只保g球
Right.
f得也是
Well, Steve told me he's offering you a new contract.
史蒂夫告V我他已提出了ms
Yes.
是的
So why did you return my call?
那你槭颤N要回我
Because it's the Red Sox.
因檫@是tm
Because I believe science might offer an answer to the Curse of the Bambino.
因槲蚁嘈趴W可以破解比斯的魔咒 (1920年tm比斯被u後{咒 tmo法再得全冠)
Because I hear you hired Bill James. Yup.
- 因槲衣f你l蛄吮.詹姆斯 -
You know, why someone took so long to hire that guy is beyond me.
槭颤N要@N久才有人l蛩 我真想不通
Well, baseball hates him.
棒球界不喜g他
Well, baseball can hate him, you know.
是的 棒球界可以他
One of the great things about money is that it buys a lot of things,
X的一大好就是可以I很多|西
one of which is the luxury to disregard what baseball likes,
@N奢侈包括了 不用管棒球界喜g什N
doesn't like, what baseball thinks, doesn't think.
棒球界不喜g什N 它怎N想 不怎N想
Ah. Sounds nice.
起砗芩
I was grateful for the call.
我很感激你的黼
You were grateful? Yeah.
- 你很感激? -
For 41 million, you built a play-off team.
你用4100f美元M建了Q球
You lost Damon, Giambi, Isringhausen, Pena,
你失去了戴蒙 吉安比 伊斯林豪森 佩{
and you won more games without them than you did with them.
然後你A的比 比他在的r候更多
You won the exact same number of games that the Yankees won,
你A的比跟洋基一佣
but the Yankees spent 1.4 million per win,
但洋基每倮平均花M1400f美元
and you paid 260,000.
而你只付出了26f美元
I know you're taking it in the teeth, but the first guy through the wall,
我知道你Dy得滴血 但第一打破牢的人
he always gets bloody.
是受挫折的
Always. This is threatening not just a way of doing business,
是 @不H威{到整I模式
but in their minds, it's threatening the game.
在他的心目中 @威{到整\永砟
Really, what it's threatening is their livelihood, their jobs.
真的 @威{到他的生存方式 他的碗
It's threatening the way that they do things.
威{到他做事的方式
Every time that happens,
每次出F@N事
whether it's a government, a way of doing business, whatever,
o是政府行 是商I行 o是什N
the people who are holding the reins,
手握掌控嗟娜
they have their hands on the switch,
可以一手遮天的人
they go batshit crazy.
他l
I mean, anybody who's not tearing their team down right now
你看 那些不拆散F有球
and rebuilding it using your model,
不按你的模式重M球的人
they're dinosaurs.
他就是缃^的恐
They'll be sitting on their ass on the sofa in October
今年10月 他坐在自家沙l上
watching the Boston Red Sox win the World Series.
眼看著波士Dtm A得世界大冠
What's this?
@是什N
I want you to be my general manager. That's my offer.
我要你我的球理 @是我_的r
Heads up.
注意啊
What was that?
你致锇
Sorry. I don't know. What the hell was that?
- 抱歉 我也不知道 - 你搞什N啊
You knucklehead.
你i^
How was Boston?
波士D之行如何
Impressive.
印象深刻
Did Henry make you a good offer, at least?
亨利o了你很好的待遇吧
Doesn't matter. Doesn't matter. What was it? What was it?
- oPo要 ]什N的 - 是怎 是怎
Doesn't matter. What was it?
- @oPo要 - 到底是什N
That makes you the highest-paid GM in the history of sports.
你是w育史上 薪水最高的理啊
So?
所以呢
So what?
又怎
I made one decision in my life based on money.
我曾做^一向X看的Q定
And I swore I would never do it again.
我l^誓 ^不再犯
You're not doing it for the money.
你@次不是榱隋X
No? No.
- 不是 - 不是
You're doing it for what the money says.
你是榱诉@X的意x
And it says what it says to any player that makes big money.
它代表著每大X的球T 都知道的意x
That they're worth it.
就是他值得@rX
What a dump.
@都什N屁
I really wanted to win here.
我真的想在@Y取得倮
I really did.
我真的想
I think you won pretty big, Billy.
我X得你已大@全倭 比利
Pete, we lost.
皮特 我了
We lost.
我了
It's only been a few days. Give yourself some time to get over it.
才滋於已 你得o自己一crg走出
Man, I don't get over these things.
夥 我永h[不了@
Ever.
永h
Come with me to the video room. I wanna show you something.
跟我到像室 有|西o你看
No, man, I'm not up for film right now.
不了 我F在]心情
Come on. Seriously.
f真的
Come on, Billy. Come on.
^ 比利 跟我
The Visalia Oaks
S塞利的W克m小盟
and our 240-pound catcher, Jeremy Brown,
以及我220斤的捕手苋鹈.布朗
who, as you know, is scared to run to second base.
你知道的 他跑二臼且他命了
This was in a game six weeks ago.
@是六周前的一霰荣
This guy's gonna start with a fastball.
@人投快球
Jeremy's gonna take him to deep center.
苋鹈滓把球打到中後方
Here's what's interesting,
@是最有趣的地方了
because Jeremy's gonna do what he never does.
因苋鹈状蛩阕 他]做^的事
He's gonna go for it.
他要拼了
He's gonna round first and he's gonna go for it.
他@^一 然後全力n向二
Okay?
浜昧
This is all of Jeremy's nightmares coming to life.
@直就是苋鹈椎呢舫烧
Aw, they're laughing at him. And Jeremy's about to find out why.
- 他在笑他 - 苋鹈遵R上就要知道槭颤N了
Jeremy's about to realize
苋鹈滓庾R到
that the ball went 60 feet over the fence.
球w出了60英尺h
He hit a home run and didn't even realize it.
他打出了全敬 而自己都]lX
How can you not be romantic about baseball?
你怎N能不凵习羟 （猛c^）
It's a metaphor. I know it's a metaphor.
- @是在[喻你 - 我知道是在f我
Okay.
好了
Pete, you're a good egg.
皮特 你是好人
I'll call you.
我打o你
Hey, Dad, this is the song I told you I'd record.
嘿 老爸 @是我f了u的歌
Please don't show it to anyone else.
不要oe人啊
Let me know if you change your mind and stay in california.
如果你改主意 留在加利福利 得告V我
If not, you're a really great dad.
即使]有 你也是最好的爸爸
* I'm just a little bit caught in the middle *
* 我有c左右呻y *
* Life is a maze And loVe is a riddle *
* 生活是座迷m 矍槭iF *
* I don't know where to go can't do it alone, I'Ve tried *
* 我不知道去哪 我o法自完成 我努力了 *
* And I don't know why *
* 我不知道槭颤N *
* I'm just a little girl Lost in the moment *
* 我只是迷失在此刻的小女孩 *
* I'm so scared But I don't show it *
* 管害怕 但我s不流露 *
* I can't figure it out It's bringing me down *
* 我]有k法 快被艨 *
* I know I'Ve got to let it go *
* 我知道 我得放手 *
* And just enjoy the show *
* 好好享受@鲂 *
* Slow it down, make it stop *
* 慢下 停下 *
* Or else my heart Is going to pop *
* 不然我的心K就要跳出砹 *
* 'cause it's too much Yeah, it's a lot *
* 因樘多 快要承受不了 *
* To be something I'm not *
* @不是我 *
* I'm a fool, out of loVe *
* 我是傻瓜 ]人 *
* And I just can't get enough *
* 可是我想要更多 *
* I'm just a little bit caught in the middle *
* 我有c左右呻y *
* Life is a maze And loVe is a riddle *
* 生活是座迷m 矍槭iF *
* I don't know where to go can't do it alone, I'Ve tried *
* 我不知道去哪 我o法自完成 我努力了 *
* And I don't know why *
* 我不知道槭颤N *
* I'm just a little girl Lost in the moment *
比利拒^tm_出的1250f美金的年薪
* I'm so scared But I don't show it *
他x窳粼W克m檫\蛹倚Я
* I know I'Ve got to let it go *
赡赆 tmA得自1918年以淼 第一座世界大冠
* And just enjoy the show *
裼玫恼是W克m的棒球哲W
* Just enjoy the show *
比利仍fDA得世界大冠
* You're such a loser, Dad Just enjoy the show *
* 你是失≌ 爸爸 享受@鲂惆 *
* You're such a loser, Dad *
* 你是失≌ 爸爸 *
* Just enjoy the show **
* 享受@鲂惆 *